<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releasedocs on Xubuntu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releasedocs on Xubuntu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 12:00:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>General Shortcut Function Super or Ctrl+Escape Show the application menu Super+F or Super+E or Ctrl+Alt+F Launch default file manager Super+L Lock the screen Super+M Launch default email client Super+P Show the display switcher popup Super+R or Alt+F2 Show the Run Application dialog Super+T or Ctrl+Alt+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+W Launch default web browser Super+F1 Show the mouse cursor position Ctrl+Alt+Delete Show the Logout dialog Ctrl+Alt+Escape Activate the kill cursor (click a window to force-close it) Ctrl+Shift+Escape Launch the Task Manager Screenshots Shortcut Function Print Take a screenshot of the full screen Alt+Print Take a screenshot of the current window Shift+Print Take a regional screenshot Multimedia Keyboard Specialty Keys Shortcut Function Calculator Launch Mate Calculator Display Show the display switcher popup Explorer Launch default file manager Homepage Launch default web browser Mail Launch default email client Music Launch Rhythmbox WWW Launch default web browser Window Management Shortcut Function Alt+Tab Cycle windows Alt+Shift+Tab Cycle windows in reverse Shift+Alt+Page_Down Minimize the current window Alt+F4 Close the current window Alt+F5 Maximize the current window horizontally Alt+F6 Maximize the current window vertically Alt+F7 Maximize the current window Alt+F8 Stick the current window Alt+F9 Minimize the current window Alt+F11 Fullscreen the current window Alt+F12 Make the current window show above other windows Super+Keypad1 Tile the current window to the bottom-left quarter Super+Keypad2 Tile the current window to the bottom half Super+Keypad3 Tile the current window to the bottom-right quarter Super+Keypad4 Tile the current window to the left half Super+Keypad6 Tile the current window to the right half Super+Keypad7 Tile the current window to the upper-left quarter Super+Keypad8 Tile the current window to the top half Super+Keypad9 Tile the current window to the upper-right quarter Shift+Alt+Page_Up Raise the current window Super+D Show the Desktop Super+Tab Show the per-application window switcher </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 21.10 &amp;ldquo;Impish Indri&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 21.10 was released on Thursday, October 14, 2021 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, June 14, 2022. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 21.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates UX Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1942987, 1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>General Shortcut Function Alt+F2 Show the Run Application dialog Ctrl+Alt+Delete Show the Logout dialog Super+L Lock the screen Ctrl+Alt+Escape Activate the kill cursor (click a window to force-close it) Super+P Show the display switcher popup Ctrl+Escape Show the application menu Ctrl+Shift+Escape Launch the Task Manager Print Take a screenshot of the full screen Alt+Print Take a screenshot of the current window Shift+Print Take a regional screenshot Super+W Launch default web browser Super+M Lauch default email client Super+F Launch default file manager Super+F1 Show the mouse cursor position Ctrl+Alt+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+R Show the Run Application dialog Super+E Launch default file manager Ctrl+Alt+F Launch default file manager Super+1 Launch Parole Media Player Super+2 Launch Pidgin Super+3 Launch LibreOffice Writer Super+4 Launch LibreOffice Calc Multimedia Keyboard Specialty Keys Shortcut Function Display Show the display switcher popup WWW Launch default web browser Homepage Launch default web browser Mail Lauch default email client Explorer Launch default file manager Calculator Launch Mate Calculator Music Launch Parole Media Player Messenger Launch Pidgin Window Management Shortcut Function Alt+Insert Create a new workspace Alt+Tab Cycle windows Alt+Shift+Tab Cycle windows in reverse Alt+Delete Delete the current workspace Ctrl+Alt+Down Move to the below workspace Ctrl+Alt+Up Move to the above workspace Ctrl+Alt+Left Move to the left workspace Ctrl+Alt+Right Move to the the right workspace Shift+Alt+Page_Down Minimize the current window Alt+F4 Close the current window Alt+F5 Maximize the current window horizontally Alt+F6 Maximize the current window vertically Alt+F7 Maximize the current window Alt+F8 Stick the current window Alt+F9 Minimize the current window Alt+F11 Fullscreen the current window Alt+F12 Make the current window show above other windows Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Left Move the current window to the left workspace Ctrl+Alt+End Move the current window to the next workspace Ctrl+Alt+Home Move the current window to the previous workspace Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Right Move the current window to the right workspace Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Up Move the current window to the above workspace Ctrl+Alt+1 Move to Workspace 1 Ctrl+Alt+2 Move to Workspace 2 Ctrl+Alt+3 Move to Workspace 3 Ctrl+Alt+4 Move to Workspace 4 Ctrl+Alt+5 Move to Workspace 5 Ctrl+Alt+6 Move to Workspace 6 Ctrl+Alt+7 Move to Workspace 7 Ctrl+Alt+8 Move to Workspace 8 Ctrl+Alt+9 Move to Workspace 9 Super+Keypad1 Tile the current window to the bottom-left quarter Super+Keypad2 Tile the current window to the bottom half Super+Keypad3 Tile the current window to the bottom-right quarter Super+Keypad4 Tile the current window to the left half Super+Keypad6 Tile the current window to the right half Super+Keypad7 Tile the current window to the upper-left quarter Super+Keypad8 Tile the current window to the top half Super+Keypad9 Tile the current window to the upper-right quarter Shift+Alt+Page_Up Raise the current window Super+D Show the Desktop Super+Tab Show the per-application window switcher Ctrl+F1 Move to Workspace 1 Ctrl+F2 Move to Workspace 2 Ctrl+F3 Move to Workspace 3 Ctrl+F4 Move to Workspace 4 Ctrl+F5 Move to Workspace 5 Ctrl+F6 Move to Workspace 6 Ctrl+F7 Move to Workspace 7 Ctrl+F8 Move to Workspace 8 Ctrl+F9 Move to Workspace 9 Ctrl+F10 Move to Workspace 10 Ctrl+F11 Move to Workspace 11 Ctrl+F12 Move to Workspace 12 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 21.04 &amp;ldquo;Hirsute Hippo&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 21.04 was released on Thursday, April 22, 2021 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, January 22, 2022. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 21.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates UX Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) General Issues Boot: Decryption password prompt not visible (1917062) GNOME Font Viewer: Crashes in the live environment (1845362) Xfce Pulseaudio Plugin: Multiple notifications displayed if multiple Pulseaudio plugins added to panel (1769775) Xfce Screensaver: Password required twice when switching users (1874178) Ubuntu Common Release Notes The main Ubuntu Release Notes covers both many of the other packages we carry and more issues common to every Ubuntu flavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 22.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 20.04 or 21.10 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read JammyUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application; In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo; if you are using 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 22.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 22.04 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read KineticUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo;, and change it if otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 23.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 23.04 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read ManticUpgrades on help.ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo;, and change it if otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 24.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 22.04 or 23.10 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read NobleUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo; if you are using 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/16.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/16.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.10 (Yakkety Yak)&#xA;Known Issues Installer Issues Various virtual machine issues can show up. More so with VirtualBox or VMWare. General Issues 792085 Automatic remount of safely removed usb 3.0 drive Xubuntu Issues 1631715 Password needed twice restarting from suspend Thunar 1311926 Thunar file order changes when renaming 1512120 Thunar crashes on file renaming 1514912 Thunar crash while copying 1540186 Thunar crash while dragging and dropping Changes Thunar Add upstream bugzilla patch to reduce crashes on file move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 17.04 (Zesty Zapus)&#xA;Xubuntu 17.04 will be supported for 9 months until January 2018. If you need Long Term Support, it is recommended you use Xubuntu 16.04 LTS instead.&#xA;Several Xfce panel plugins and applications have been ported to GTK+ 3, paving the way for improved theming and further development. Core Xfce libraries exo and libxfce4ui have also been updated with full GTK+ 3 support, the latter adding support for Glade development in Xubuntu with the installation of &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;libxfce4ui-glade&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Notable Changes Incompatibility with BIOS in certain Lenovo, Acer systems A bug in the Linux 4.13 kernel shipped in Ubuntu 17.10 can leave users unable to update any of their BIOS settings, including their system’s boot order, after booting this version of Ubuntu.&#xA;A kernel with a fix for this issue will be available in zesty-updates shortly, but, the Ubuntu 17.10 installer images still contain the kernel with this bug. Users with affected systems should not upgrade to Ubuntu 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Notable Issues Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation. We do however aim to test all the possible methods of installation (including for OEM and using encryption) available either on a virtual machine or on hardware (where hardware has been used during testing then Xubuntu QA will where possible make that known on the iso testing tracker).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading from 18.04 For 32 bit installations this is disabled and currently out of our control.&#xA;Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation. We do however aim to test all the possible methods of installation (including for OEM and using encryption) available either on a virtual machine or on hardware (where hardware has been used during testing then Xubuntu QA will where possible make that known on the iso testing tracker).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Dropping 32-bit Images In December, the team voted to discontinue 32-bit images for Xubuntu 19.04 and forward. If you want to continue using Xubuntu with 32-bit architectures, Xubuntu 18.04 is supported for 3 years, and the Xubuntu package set can be installed from the Minimal CD.&#xA;Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Known Issues Installer Issues System doesn&amp;rsquo;t boot after installation - Legacy mode / 2 disks (1847898) General Issues GNOME Font Viewer: Crashes in the live environment (1845362) Ubiquity: Chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Xfce Pulseaudio Plugin: Multiple notifications displayed if multiple Pulseaudio plugins added to panel (1769775) Xfce Task Manager: Tooltips become unresponsive (1740578, fix committed upstream) Ubuntu Generic Release Note The main Ubuntu release note covers both many of the other packages we carry and more generic issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 20.04 &amp;ldquo;Focal Fossa&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 20.04 was released on Thursday, April 23, 2020 and will be supported for three years until Saturday, April 29, 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 20.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Screenshots Major Updates Removals Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues System doesn&amp;rsquo;t boot after installation - Legacy mode / 2 disks (1847898) grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Graphical Issues AMD Graphics: Block staircase display with side-by-side monitors of different pixel widths (1873895, Fixed upstream, SRU expected for 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 20.10 &amp;ldquo;Groovy Gorilla&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 20.10 was released on Thursday, October 22, 2020 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, July 22, 2021. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 20.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Removals Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Graphical Issues AMD Graphics: Block staircase display with side-by-side monitors of different pixel widths (1873895, Fixed upstream, SRU expected for 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 22.04 &amp;ldquo;Jammy Jellyfish&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 22.04 will be released on Thursday, April 21, 2022, and will be supported for three years until April 2025. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 22.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1942987, 1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 22.10 &amp;ldquo;Kinetic Kudu&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 22.10 will be released on Thursday, October 20, 2022, and will be supported for nine months until July 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 22.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 23.04 &amp;ldquo;Lunar Lobster&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 23.04 was be released on Thursday, April 20, 2023, and will be supported for nine months until January 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 23.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 23.10 &amp;ldquo;Mantic Minotaur&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 23.10 was released on Thursday, October 12, 2023, and will be supported for nine months until July 2024. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 23.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Appearance Updates Hardware Support Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 24.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 24.04 &amp;ldquo;Noble Numbat&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04 was released on Thursday, April 25, 2024, and will be supported for three years until April 2027. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 24.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues GRUB menu not displayed for dual-boot system installation (2060624) Installer may select two root (/) partitions (2060896) No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
