<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xubuntu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xubuntu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:00:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 24.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/24.04/xubuntu-24-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/24.04/xubuntu-24-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 24.04.&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04, codenamed Noble Numbat, is a long-term support (LTS) release and will be supported for 3 years, until 2027.&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04, featuring the latest updates from Xfce 4.18 and GNOME 46.&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04 features the latest updates from Xfce 4.18, GNOME 46, and MATE 1.26. For new users and those coming from Xubuntu 22.04, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the performance, stability, and improved hardware support found in Xubuntu 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/23.10/xubuntu-23-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 17:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/23.10/xubuntu-23-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 23.10.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.10, codenamed Mantic Minotaur, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2024.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.10, featuring the latest updates from Xfce 4.18 and GNOME 44.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.10 features the latest updates from Xfce 4.18, GNOME 45, and MATE 1.26. With a focus on stability, memory management, and hardware support, Xubuntu 23.10 should perform well on your device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/23.04/xubuntu-23-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/23.04/xubuntu-23-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 23.04.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.04, codenamed Lunar Lobster, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until January 2024.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.04, featuring the latest updates from Xfce 4.18 and GNOME 44.&#xA;Xubuntu 23.04 features the latest Xfce 4.18. Xfce 4.18 delivers a stable desktop environment with a number of performance improvements and new features to enjoy. In particular, the Thunar file manager benefits from a new image preview feature, undo and redo functionality, file highlights, and recursive search.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.10/xubuntu-22-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.10/xubuntu-22-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 22.10.&#xA;Xubuntu 22.10, codenamed Kinetic Kudu, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2023.&#xA;Xubuntu 22.10, featuring the latest updates from Xfce 4.17, GNOME 43, and MATE 1.26. Xubuntu 22.10 features the latest updates from Xfce 4.17, GNOME 43, and MATE 1.26. The &amp;ldquo;bleeding edge&amp;rdquo; Xfce 4.17 components are included as an early preview to the upcoming Xfce 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 22:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 22.04.&#xA;Xubuntu 22.04, codenamed Jammy Jellyfish, is a long-term support (LTS) release and will be supported for 3 years, until 2025.&#xA;The Xubuntu and Xfce development teams have made great strides in usability, expanded features, and additional applications in the last two years. Users coming from 20.04 will be delighted with improvements found in Xfce 4.16 and our expanded application set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04 Community Wallpaper Contest Winners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 22:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the results of the 22.04 community wallpaper contest!&#xA;As always, we&amp;rsquo;d like to send out a huge thanks to every contestant. The Xubuntu Community Wallpaper Contest gives us a unique chance to interact with the community and get contributions from members who may otherwise not have had the opportunity to join in before. With around 130 submissions, the contest garnered less interest this time around, but we still had a lot of great work to pick from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04 Community Wallpaper Contest</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/22.04/xubuntu-22-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</guid>
      <description>We’re on our way to the 22.04 LTS release and it’s time for another community wallpaper contest!&#xA;How to participate? For a chance to win, submit your submission at contest.xubuntu.org.&#xA;Important dates Start of submissions: Immediately Submission deadline: March 12th, 2022 Announcement of selections: Late March All dates are in UTC.&#xA;Contest terms All submissions must adhere to the Terms and Guidelines, including specifics about subject matter, image resolution and attribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.10/xubuntu-21-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.10/xubuntu-21-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 21.10.&#xA;Xubuntu 21.10, codenamed Impish Indri, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until June 2022. If you need a stable environment with longer support time we recommend that you use Xubuntu 20.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/download/.&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>General Shortcut Function Super or Ctrl+Escape Show the application menu Super+F or Super+E or Ctrl+Alt+F Launch default file manager Super+L Lock the screen Super+M Launch default email client Super+P Show the display switcher popup Super+R or Alt+F2 Show the Run Application dialog Super+T or Ctrl+Alt+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+W Launch default web browser Super+F1 Show the mouse cursor position Ctrl+Alt+Delete Show the Logout dialog Ctrl+Alt+Escape Activate the kill cursor (click a window to force-close it) Ctrl+Shift+Escape Launch the Task Manager Screenshots Shortcut Function Print Take a screenshot of the full screen Alt+Print Take a screenshot of the current window Shift+Print Take a regional screenshot Multimedia Keyboard Specialty Keys Shortcut Function Calculator Launch Mate Calculator Display Show the display switcher popup Explorer Launch default file manager Homepage Launch default web browser Mail Launch default email client Music Launch Rhythmbox WWW Launch default web browser Window Management Shortcut Function Alt+Tab Cycle windows Alt+Shift+Tab Cycle windows in reverse Shift+Alt+Page_Down Minimize the current window Alt+F4 Close the current window Alt+F5 Maximize the current window horizontally Alt+F6 Maximize the current window vertically Alt+F7 Maximize the current window Alt+F8 Stick the current window Alt+F9 Minimize the current window Alt+F11 Fullscreen the current window Alt+F12 Make the current window show above other windows Super+Keypad1 Tile the current window to the bottom-left quarter Super+Keypad2 Tile the current window to the bottom half Super+Keypad3 Tile the current window to the bottom-right quarter Super+Keypad4 Tile the current window to the left half Super+Keypad6 Tile the current window to the right half Super+Keypad7 Tile the current window to the upper-left quarter Super+Keypad8 Tile the current window to the top half Super+Keypad9 Tile the current window to the upper-right quarter Shift+Alt+Page_Up Raise the current window Super+D Show the Desktop Super+Tab Show the per-application window switcher </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 21.10 &amp;ldquo;Impish Indri&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 21.10 was released on Thursday, October 14, 2021 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, June 14, 2022. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 21.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates UX Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1942987, 1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>General Shortcut Function Alt+F2 Show the Run Application dialog Ctrl+Alt+Delete Show the Logout dialog Super+L Lock the screen Ctrl+Alt+Escape Activate the kill cursor (click a window to force-close it) Super+P Show the display switcher popup Ctrl+Escape Show the application menu Ctrl+Shift+Escape Launch the Task Manager Print Take a screenshot of the full screen Alt+Print Take a screenshot of the current window Shift+Print Take a regional screenshot Super+W Launch default web browser Super+M Lauch default email client Super+F Launch default file manager Super+F1 Show the mouse cursor position Ctrl+Alt+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+T Launch default terminal emulator Super+R Show the Run Application dialog Super+E Launch default file manager Ctrl+Alt+F Launch default file manager Super+1 Launch Parole Media Player Super+2 Launch Pidgin Super+3 Launch LibreOffice Writer Super+4 Launch LibreOffice Calc Multimedia Keyboard Specialty Keys Shortcut Function Display Show the display switcher popup WWW Launch default web browser Homepage Launch default web browser Mail Lauch default email client Explorer Launch default file manager Calculator Launch Mate Calculator Music Launch Parole Media Player Messenger Launch Pidgin Window Management Shortcut Function Alt+Insert Create a new workspace Alt+Tab Cycle windows Alt+Shift+Tab Cycle windows in reverse Alt+Delete Delete the current workspace Ctrl+Alt+Down Move to the below workspace Ctrl+Alt+Up Move to the above workspace Ctrl+Alt+Left Move to the left workspace Ctrl+Alt+Right Move to the the right workspace Shift+Alt+Page_Down Minimize the current window Alt+F4 Close the current window Alt+F5 Maximize the current window horizontally Alt+F6 Maximize the current window vertically Alt+F7 Maximize the current window Alt+F8 Stick the current window Alt+F9 Minimize the current window Alt+F11 Fullscreen the current window Alt+F12 Make the current window show above other windows Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Left Move the current window to the left workspace Ctrl+Alt+End Move the current window to the next workspace Ctrl+Alt+Home Move the current window to the previous workspace Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Right Move the current window to the right workspace Ctrl+Shift+Alt+Up Move the current window to the above workspace Ctrl+Alt+1 Move to Workspace 1 Ctrl+Alt+2 Move to Workspace 2 Ctrl+Alt+3 Move to Workspace 3 Ctrl+Alt+4 Move to Workspace 4 Ctrl+Alt+5 Move to Workspace 5 Ctrl+Alt+6 Move to Workspace 6 Ctrl+Alt+7 Move to Workspace 7 Ctrl+Alt+8 Move to Workspace 8 Ctrl+Alt+9 Move to Workspace 9 Super+Keypad1 Tile the current window to the bottom-left quarter Super+Keypad2 Tile the current window to the bottom half Super+Keypad3 Tile the current window to the bottom-right quarter Super+Keypad4 Tile the current window to the left half Super+Keypad6 Tile the current window to the right half Super+Keypad7 Tile the current window to the upper-left quarter Super+Keypad8 Tile the current window to the top half Super+Keypad9 Tile the current window to the upper-right quarter Shift+Alt+Page_Up Raise the current window Super+D Show the Desktop Super+Tab Show the per-application window switcher Ctrl+F1 Move to Workspace 1 Ctrl+F2 Move to Workspace 2 Ctrl+F3 Move to Workspace 3 Ctrl+F4 Move to Workspace 4 Ctrl+F5 Move to Workspace 5 Ctrl+F6 Move to Workspace 6 Ctrl+F7 Move to Workspace 7 Ctrl+F8 Move to Workspace 8 Ctrl+F9 Move to Workspace 9 Ctrl+F10 Move to Workspace 10 Ctrl+F11 Move to Workspace 11 Ctrl+F12 Move to Workspace 12 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/21.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 21.04 &amp;ldquo;Hirsute Hippo&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 21.04 was released on Thursday, April 22, 2021 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, January 22, 2022. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 21.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates UX Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) General Issues Boot: Decryption password prompt not visible (1917062) GNOME Font Viewer: Crashes in the live environment (1845362) Xfce Pulseaudio Plugin: Multiple notifications displayed if multiple Pulseaudio plugins added to panel (1769775) Xfce Screensaver: Password required twice when switching users (1874178) Ubuntu Common Release Notes The main Ubuntu Release Notes covers both many of the other packages we carry and more issues common to every Ubuntu flavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.04/xubuntu-21-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.04/xubuntu-21-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 21.04.&#xA;Xubuntu 21.04, codenamed Hirsute Hippo, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until January 2022. If you need a stable environment with longer support time we recommend that you use Xubuntu 20.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/download/.&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04 Testing Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.04/xubuntu-21-04-testing-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/21.04/xubuntu-21-04-testing-week/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re participating in another ‘Ubuntu Testing Week’ from April 1st to April 7th with other flavours in the Ubuntu family. On April 1st, the beta version of Xubuntu 21.04 ‘Hirsute Hippo’ will be released after halting all new changes to its features, user interface and documentation. Between April 1st and the final release on April 22nd, all efforts by the Xubuntu team and community should be focused on ISO testing, reporting bugs, fixing bugs, and translations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.10/xubuntu-20-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.10/xubuntu-20-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 20.10!&#xA;Xubuntu 20.10, codenamed Groovy Gorilla, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2021. If you need a stable environment with longer support time we recommend that you use Xubuntu 20.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/download/.&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu is now on GitHub!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/xubuntu-is-now-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 21:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/xubuntu-is-now-on-github/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, May 18th, the Xubuntu Team voted to migrate some of our infrastructure away from Launchpad to GitHub for code hosting, while translations are now on Transifex. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of the changes:&#xA;We have a new GitHub organization, under the Xubuntu name. Each subteam has an equivalent in the new organization. All codebases have been migrated to GitHub. All translations have moved to Transifex. Every codebase moved to GitHub has been mirrored on Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 17:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 20.04. Xubuntu 20.04, codenamed Focal Fossa, is a long-term support (LTS) release and will be supported for 3 years, until April 2023.&#xA;The Xubuntu team has been hard at work for the last six months of this development cycle improving both the Xfce desktop environment and the Xubuntu user experience following our 19.10 release, which introduced Xfce 4.14 for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 Community Wallpaper Contest Winners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 03:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team are happy to announce the results of the 20.04 community wallpaper contest!&#xA;We want to send out a huge thanks to every contestant. Each contest becomes more and more successful. For the 16.04 contest, we had 92 submissions; For 18.04 there were 162; and this time around there was an incredible 237 submissions! Great work! All of the submissions are browsable on the 20.04 contest page at contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 Testing Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-testing-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 06:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-testing-week/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re participating in an ‘Ubuntu Testing Week’ from April 2nd to April 8th with other flavors in the Ubuntu family. On April 2nd, we’ll be releasing the beta release of Xubuntu 20.04 LTS, after halting all new changes to its features, user interface and documentation. And between April 2nd and the final release on April 23rd, all efforts by the Xubuntu team and community are focused on ISO testing, bug reporting, and fixing bugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 community wallpaper contest</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/20.04/xubuntu-20-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</guid>
      <description>We’re on our way to the 20.04 LTS release and it’s time for another community wallpaper contest!&#xA;How to participate? For a chance to win, submit your submission at contest.xubuntu.org.&#xA;Important dates Start of submissions: Immediately Submission deadline: March 13th, 2020 Announcement of selections: Late March All dates are in UTC.&#xA;Contest terms All submissions must adhere to the Terms and Guidelines, including specifics about subject matter, image resolution and attribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/19.10/xubuntu-19-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 18:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/19.10/xubuntu-19-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 19.10!&#xA;Xubuntu 19.10, codenamed Eoan Ermine, is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2020. If you need a stable environment with longer support time, we recommend that you use Xubuntu 18.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/19.04/xubuntu-19-04-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/19.04/xubuntu-19-04-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 19.04!&#xA;Xubuntu 19.04 is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until January 2020. If you need a stable environment with longer support time, we recommend that you use Xubuntu 18.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.10/xubuntu-18-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 23:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.10/xubuntu-18-10-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 18.10!&#xA;Xubuntu 18.10 is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2019. If you need a stable environment with longer support time, we recommend that you use Xubuntu 18.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04.1 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/18-04-1-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 19:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/18-04-1-released/</guid>
      <description>The first point release for 18.04 Bionic Beaver has now been released.&#xA;As usual, this point release includes many updates, and updated installation media has been provided so that fewer updates will need to be downloaded after installation. These include security updates and corrections for other high-impact bugs, with a focus on maintaining stability and compatibility with Ubuntu 18.04 LTS.&#xA;The point release images are available as torrents and direct downloads immediately from xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10 EOL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-eol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 05:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-eol/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday 19th July 2018, Xubuntu 17.10 goes End of Life (EOL). For more information please see the Ubuntu 17.10 EOL Notice.&#xA;We strongly recommend upgrading to the current release, Xubuntu 18.04, as soon as practical. Alternatively you can download the current Xubuntu release and install fresh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Wiki pages for Testers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/new-wiki-pages-for-testers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 16:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/new-wiki-pages-for-testers/</guid>
      <description>During the last few weeks of the 18.04 (Bionic Beaver) cycle, we had 2 people drop by in our development channel trying to respond to the call for testers from the Development and QA Teams.&#xA;It quickly became apparent to me that I was having to repeat myself in order to make it &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; enough for someone who had never tested for us, to understand what I was trying to put across.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/xubuntu-18-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 23:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/xubuntu-18-04-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 18.04. Xubuntu 18.04 is a long-term support (LTS) release and will be supported for 3 years, until April 2021.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads immediately from xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/. As the main server and mirrors might be busy for the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.&#xA;Xubuntu Core, our minimal installation option, is available to download from unit193.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04 Community Wallpaper Contest Winners!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/18-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 22:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/18-04-community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team are happy to announce the results of the 18.04 community wallpaper contest!&#xA;We want to send out a huge thanks to every contestant; last time we had 92 submissions but now you all made us work much harder in picking the best ones out with a total of 162 submissions! Great work! All of the submissions are browsable on the 18.04 contest page at contest.xubuntu.org.&#xA;Without further ado, here are the winners:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing for Xubuntu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/testing-for-xubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 08:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/testing-for-xubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 18.04 “Bionic Beaver” is just around the corner. The first beta milestone arrives next week, and the final release is a little over a month away. 18.04 is an LTS release, meaning it has a 3-year support cycle and is definitely recommended for all users. Or it would be, if we knew it was ready. Stick around&amp;hellip; this is a bit of a long read, but it’s important.&#xA;The ISO Tracker has seen little activity for the last few development cycles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04 community wallpaper contest</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/xubuntu-18-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/18.04/xubuntu-18-04-community-wallpaper-contest/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re on our way to the 18.04 LTS release and it&amp;rsquo;s time for another community wallpaper contest!&#xA;How to participate? For a chance to win, submit your submission at contest.xubuntu.org.&#xA;Important dates Start of submissions: Immediately Submission deadline: March 15th, 2018 Announcement of selections: Late March All dates are in UTC.&#xA;Contest terms All submissions must adhere to the Terms and Guidelines, including specifics about subject matter, image resolution and attribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10.1 Release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 17:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-1-release/</guid>
      <description>Following the recent testing of a respin to deal with the BIOS bug on some Lenovo machines, Xubuntu 17.10.1 has been released. Official download sources have been updated to point to this point release, but if you&amp;rsquo;re using a mirror, be sure you are downloading the 17.10**.1** version.&#xA;No changes to applications are included, however, this release does include any updates made between the original release date and now.&#xA;Note: Even with this fix, you will want to update your system to make sure you get all security fixes since the ISO respin, including the one for Meltdown, addressed in USN-3523, which you can read more about here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.04 End Of Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.04/17-04-eol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.04/17-04-eol/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday 13th January 2018, Xubuntu 17.04 goes End of Life (EOL). For more information please see the Ubuntu 17.04 EOL Notice.&#xA;We strongly recommend upgrading to the current regular release, Xubuntu 17.10.1, as soon as practical. Alternatively you can download the current Xubuntu release and install fresh.&#xA;The 17.10.1 release recently saw testing across all flavors to address the BIOS bug found after its release in October 2017. Updated and bugfree ISO files are now available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 16:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.10/xubuntu-17-10-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 17.10.&#xA;Xubuntu 17.10 is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until July 2018. If you need a stable environment with longer support time, we recommend that you use Xubuntu 16.04 LTS instead, or wait for 18.04, the next LTS version to be released in April 2018.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Quality Assurance team is spreading out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/xubuntu-quality-assurance-team-spreading-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 16:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/xubuntu-quality-assurance-team-spreading-out/</guid>
      <description>Up until the start of the 17.04 cycle the Xubuntu Quality Assurance team had been led by one person. During the last cycle, a break was needed by that person. The recent addition of Dave Pearson to the team meant we were in a position to call on someone else to lead the team.&#xA;Today, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that Dave will be carrying on as a team lead. However, starting with the artfully named Artful Aardvark cycle, we will migrate to a Quality Assurance team with two leads who will be sharing duties during development cycles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.04/xubuntu-17-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/17.04/xubuntu-17-04-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 17.04.&#xA;Xubuntu 17.04 is a regular release and will be supported for 9 months, until January 2018. If you need a stable environment with longer support time, we recommend that you use Xubuntu 16.04 LTS instead.&#xA;The final release images are available as torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server might be busy in the first few days after the release, we recommend using the torrents if possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winners of the #lovexubuntu Competition!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/winners-lovexubuntu-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 20:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/winners-lovexubuntu-competition/</guid>
      <description>As Xubuntu&amp;rsquo;s tenth anniversary year is now over, it&amp;rsquo;s time to announce the winners of the #lovexubuntu competition announced in June!&#xA;The two grand prize winners, receiving a t-shirt and a sticker set, are Keith I Myers with his Xubuntu cookie cutters and Daniel Eriksson with a story of a happy customer. The three other finalists, each one receiving a set of Xubuntu stickers are Dina, Sabrin Islam and Michael Morozov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Xubuntu Council</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/introducing-xubuntu-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 16:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/introducing-xubuntu-council/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of 2016 the Xubuntu team started a process to transition the project to become council-run rather than having a single project leader. After careful planning, writing and approving the general direction, the team was ready to vote on for the first three members of the council for the project.&#xA;In this article we explain what the new Xubuntu Council is and who the council members are.&#xA;What is the Xubuntu Council about?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating releases to the website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/integrating-releases-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/integrating-releases-website/</guid>
      <description>During 2016, the Xubuntu website team has been working on integrating the releases better to the website. What this essentially means is that the maintenance is easier for the team in the future, but also that the release information is presented in a more concise and central way for each release.&#xA;Release pages We finally have a one-stop page for all currently supported releases – the Releases landing page. You can find the page at any time under the About menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presenting the Xubuntu status tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/presenting-xubuntu-status-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 10:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/presenting-xubuntu-status-tracker/</guid>
      <description>Status tracking is useful for all kinds of projects, including Xubuntu. Amongst other things, it allows contributors to quickly see what&amp;rsquo;s left to do and what others are working on. When the tracking data is kept up to date, the resulting data can be immensely helpful.&#xA;Until 2015, the Xubuntu team had been using the common status tracker for Ubuntu teams. For a reason or another, it suddenly stopped working as tracking data from Launchpad didn&amp;rsquo;t make it into the tracker database.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.10 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.10/xubuntu-16-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.10/xubuntu-16-10-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 16.10. Xubuntu 16.10 is a normal release and will be supported for 9 months.&#xA;This release has seen little visible change since April&amp;rsquo;s 16.04, however much has been done towards supplying Xubuntu with Xfce packages built with GTK3, including the porting of many plugins and Xfce Terminal to GTK3. Those GTK3 ports can, if one wishes to test them, be installed from one of the team&amp;rsquo;s development PPAs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRU for 16.04: Intel cursor bug fix released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/sru-16-04-intel-cursor-bug-fix-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/sru-16-04-intel-cursor-bug-fix-released/</guid>
      <description>When we announced the release of Xubuntu 16.04 back in April there were a few known issues, but none has been more frustrating to users than this one:&#xA;When returning from lock, the cursor disappears on the desktop, you can bring the cursor back with Ctrl+Alt+F1 followed by Ctrl+Alt+F7&#xA;Most of the other bugs were fixed by the time 16.04.1 was released in July, but this one lingered while developers tested the xserver-xorg-video-intel package that had the fix in the proposed repository in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04.1 Release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-1-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 16.04.1 Xubuntu 16.04 is an LTS (Long-Term Support) release and will be supported for 3 years with point releases appearing at regular intervals.&#xA;The release images are available as Torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;During the next few days the upgrade from 14.04 to 16.04.1 will become available via the update-manager.&#xA;Those upgrading from 14.04 should take note of the following 2 issues which affect us particularly, details of these and other bugs are further detailed at the Release Notes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for memorable and fun Xubuntu stories!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/looking-memorable-fun-xubuntu-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2016/looking-memorable-fun-xubuntu-stories/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate Xubuntu&amp;rsquo;s tenth birthday*, the Xubuntu team is glad to announce a new campaign and competition!&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for your most memorable and fun Xubuntu story. In order to participate, submit the story to xubuntu-contacts@lists.ubuntu.com. Or you may share an image (photo, drawing, painting, etc) to Elizabeth K. Joseph &amp;lt;lyz@ubuntu.com&amp;gt; and Pasi Lallinaho &amp;lt;pasi@shimmerproject.org&amp;gt;, please restrict your file size to a maximum of 5M.&#xA;For example, have you shared Xubuntu with a friend or family member, and had them react in a memorable way?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 16.04. Xubuntu 16.04 is an LTS (Long-Term Support) release and will be supported for 3 years.&#xA;The final release images are available as Torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first few days after release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.&#xA;Xubuntu 16.04 LTS release art Support For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a complete list of methods to get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04 Wallpaper Competition Winners!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-wallpaper-competition-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-wallpaper-competition-winners/</guid>
      <description>Today, the Xubuntu team are happy to announce the results of the 16.04 wallpaper competition in preparation for the 16.04 release only a few days from now!&#xA;Before we go into the results, we want to thank everyone who contributed to the competition! In total we had 92 submissions, which is over 10% more than for the 14.04 competition. Great work!&#xA;While we originally announced that we would be picking 6 winners, we eventually decided to pick a total of 10 winners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Wallpapers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-wallpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-wallpapers/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;We have talked about customizing in this series before, but now we take a look at another aspect of it – wallpapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My media manager: Other alternatives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-other-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 19:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-other-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS will be the first Xubuntu release without a default media manager. To help those without a favorite one, we’ve put up this series where some of the Xubuntu team members talk about their favorite media managers. Later in the series we discuss some cloud services and other media manager options in the Ubuntu repositories. Enjoy!&#xA;In the concluding article of this series, we will go through alternative media managers and audio players found in the Ubuntu repositories along with some comments from their contributors and users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Panel layouts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-panel-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 20:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-panel-layouts/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;In 2015, the Xubuntu team created and introduced the Xfce4 Panel Switch, a tool that allows you to work efficiently with panel layouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My media manager: The cloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 20:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS will be the first Xubuntu release without a default media manager. To help those without a favorite one, we&amp;rsquo;ve put up this series where some of the Xubuntu team members talk about their favorite media managers. Later in the series we discuss some cloud services and other media manager options in the Ubuntu repositories. Enjoy!&#xA;In addition to the more traditional media managers which manage local collections, more and more people use cloud based streaming services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Personal information integration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-personal-information-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 16:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-personal-information-integration/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;We have talked about customizing in this series before, but now we take a look at another aspect of it; personal information and its integration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Text editor and terminal color schemes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-text-editor-terminal-color-schemes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 23:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-text-editor-terminal-color-schemes/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;Customization is one of the strengths of Xubuntu and Xfce alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Window manager shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-window-manager-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 15:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-window-manager-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;Last time we talked about the default, application shortcut keys in Xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My media manager: gmusicbrowser</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-gmusicbrowser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 18:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-gmusicbrowser/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS will be the first Xubuntu release without a default media manager. To help those without a favorite one, we&amp;rsquo;ve put up this series where some of the Xubuntu team members talk about their favorite media managers. Later in the series we discuss some cloud services and other media manager options in the Ubuntu repositories. Enjoy!&#xA;This time we&amp;rsquo;re covering the latest (and for now, the last) default media manager in Xubuntu – gmusicbrowser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Shortcut keys</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-shortcut-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 23:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-shortcut-keys/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;Xubuntu comes with some useful shortcut keys by default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Menu editing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-menu-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 22:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-menu-editing/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;The application menus offer access to all installed applications on the system, whether it was shipped by default or installed a minute ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The small details: Theme configuration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-theme-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 20:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/the-small-details/small-details-theme-configuration/</guid>
      <description>In this series the Xubuntu team present some of the smaller details in Xubuntu to help you use your system more efficiently. Several of the features covered in this series are new for those who will be upgrading from 14.04 LTS to 16.04 LTS. We will also cover some features that have been in Xubuntu for longer, for those that are completely new to the operating system.&#xA;Customization is one of the strengths of Xubuntu and Xfce alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My media manager: Clementine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-clementine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/my-media-manager/my-media-manager-clementine/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS will be the first Xubuntu release without a default media manager. To help those without a favorite one, we&amp;rsquo;ve put up this series where some of the Xubuntu team members talk about their favorite media managers. Later in the series we discuss some cloud services and other media manager options in the Ubuntu repositories. Enjoy!&#xA;This time we&amp;rsquo;re covering the favorite media manager for several people working with the Quality Assurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Small and the Noisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/small-and-noisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 23:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/small-and-noisy/</guid>
      <description>In anticipation of the Xubuntu 16.04 LTS release, the Xubuntu team has prepared some treats for the blog to make the countdown even more enjoyable and exciting! Starting from this week, we will publish articles in two different article series. Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s waiting for you!&#xA;My media manager As announced before, Xubuntu 16.04 LTS will not come with a default media manager. In this series some of the Xubuntu team members talk about a few of their favorite media players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS Beta 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-lts-beta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-lts-beta-2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 16.04 LTS Beta 2. This is the final beta towards the final release in April.&#xA;Any new updates to packages should be bug fixes only, the Xubuntu team is committed to fixing as many of the bugs as possible before the final release.&#xA;Please note! Minimal upgrade testing was undertaken during this milestone. There are issues currently when upgrading to Xenial Xerus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04 Wallpaper Competition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-wallpaper-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 19:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-wallpaper-competition/</guid>
      <description>As we start counting down for the release, we are collecting submissions for the community wallpapers package (xubuntu-community-wallpapers) in Xubuntu 16.04 LTS.&#xA;How to participate? For a chance to win, send your submission at http://contest.xubuntu.org/.&#xA;Important dates Start of submissions: Immediately Submission deadline: April 1 Announcement of selections: Week 14 (some time between April 4 and April 10) All dates are in UTC.&#xA;Contest terms All submissions must adhere to the Terms and Guidelines, including specifics about subject matter, image resolution and attribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04 LTS Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-lts-beta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/xubuntu-16-04-lts-beta-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 16.04 LTS Beta 1. This is the first beta towards the final release in April.&#xA;The first beta release also marks the end of the period to land new features in the form of Ubuntu Feature Freeze. This means any new updates to packages should be bug fixes only, the Xubuntu team is committed to fixing as many of the bugs as possible before the final release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at The Working Centre&#39;s Computer Recycling Project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-the-working-centres-computer-recycling-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-the-working-centres-computer-recycling-project/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this &amp;ldquo;Xubuntu at..&amp;rdquo; series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you’re doing with us please contact Elizabeth K. Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Recently Charles McColm and Paul Nijjar took time to write to us about their work at The Working Centre&amp;rsquo;s Computer Recycling Project in Kitchener, Ontario, Canada where they&amp;rsquo;re using Xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at FreeGeek Chicago</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-freegeek-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 19:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-freegeek-chicago/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this “Xubuntu at..” series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you’re doing with us please contact Elizabeth K. Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Several months ago we learned from Evelyn Lopez at FreeGeek Chicago that they&amp;rsquo;d been deploying Xubuntu on computers they sell through their efforts to recycle used computers and parts to provide functional computers, education, internet access and job skills training to those who want them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Xubuntu documentation package locally</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/building-xubuntu-documentation-package-locally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 20:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/building-xubuntu-documentation-package-locally/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu documentation, shipped with every release of Xubuntu, is in fact a package that can be built locally, on your computer.&#xA;By default, Xubuntu does not come with the tools required to build the documentation package, so there is the need to prepare your system to be able to do it, by installing the required prerequisite packages. To do this, run the following command:&#xA;sudo apt-get build-dep xubuntu-docs&#xA;Additionally, if you are running a release earlier than 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16.04 Package Testing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/16-04-package-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 22:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/16.04/16-04-package-testing/</guid>
      <description>It is early for a post on the website from the Quality Assurance team, but we&amp;rsquo;re just about to start testing a release that will be supported for more than the regular 9 months&amp;hellip;&#xA;General testing outlook for Xenial During the next 26 weeks, we are going to be concentrating on the applications that we have in Xubuntu. This is a change from the last couple of cycles, where the emphasis has been more on the ISOs than the applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 14:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.10!&#xA;The release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/.&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a complete list of methods to get help.&#xA;Highlights and Known Issues Highlights The 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printable and shareable Xubuntu flyers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/printable-shareable-xubuntu-flyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 19:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/printable-shareable-xubuntu-flyers/</guid>
      <description>During the Wily Werewolf development cycle, the Xubuntu Marketing team has completed work on flyers that can now be printed by anyone wishing to promote Xubuntu at conferences, global jams, release parties and other events.&#xA;Flyers can be printed at home or with any typical printing service. A successful trial run of 25 US letter-sized flyers was completed in August by our marketing lead:&#xA;Find the links to the flyer as well as all translated versions on the Products page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.10 Final Beta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-final-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 23:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-final-beta/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.10 Beta 2. This is the last beta towards the final release in October.&#xA;The Beta release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads fromhttp://cdimages.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/wily/beta-2/&#xA;Highlights and known issues New features and enhancements Xfce4 Panel Switch added, giving the ability to backup and restore existing panel layout. In addition 5 preset panel layouts are available A new window manager theme, greybird accessibility is now available Known Issues Some issues during testing of image were found, in addition some bugs related to Xubuntu have been noted during the development cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.10 Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-beta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 14:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/xubuntu-15-10-beta-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.10 Beta 1. This is the first beta towards the final release in October.&#xA;The first beta release also marks the end of the period to land new features in the form of Ubuntu Feature Freeze. This means any new updates to packages should be bug fixes only, the Xubuntu team is committed to fixing as many of the bugs as possible before the final release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artwork Project for 15.10: Making LibreOffice look integrated</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/artwork-project-for-15-10-making-libreoffice-look-integrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 21:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.10/artwork-project-for-15-10-making-libreoffice-look-integrated/</guid>
      <description>The Document Foundation http://www.documentfoundation.org&#xA;Many users or members of the community will know this already, but just for the sake of clarity: Xubuntu 15.10 Wily Werewolf will be the first release to ship LibreOffice by default. This has been a long-standing and often-repeated request so we decided to try and evaluate this on our way to the next LTS release, which will be 16.04.&#xA;Consequently, we started evaluating LibreOffice&amp;rsquo;s integration in our Desktop Environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at Colegio Hispano Americano</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-colegio-hispano-americano/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 19:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-colegio-hispano-americano/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this “Xubuntu at..” series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you’re doing with us please contact Elizabeth K. Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;As we&amp;rsquo;ve covered in other articles in this series, Xubuntu is being used world wide to serve a variety of communities with users of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at Computer Reach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-computer-reach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-computer-reach/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this &amp;ldquo;Xubuntu at..&amp;rdquo; series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you’re doing with us please contact Elizabeth K. Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Last month we started a dialog with Kevin Driscoll, PC/Linux Technical Consultant, and Dave Sevick, Executive Director, of Computer Reach to learn more about how they&amp;rsquo;re using Xubuntu in their organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Xubuntu core</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/introducing-xubuntu-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 07:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015/introducing-xubuntu-core/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu core is a slimmed down version of Xubuntu that doesn’t come with all the additional features of a full and modern desktop. We essentially only ship Xfce and the basic look and feel of Xubuntu, so there will be no office suite, media players, et cetera.&#xA;The obvious benefit is that this ISO (about 600MB) will be faster to download – especially interesting for those with limited connectivity – and fit on a CD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04 End of Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/xubuntu-12-04-end-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 19:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/xubuntu-12-04-end-of-life/</guid>
      <description>A few days after we welcomed Vivid Vervet 15.04 as the latest stable version, we see the oldest of our LTS versions go EOL. Xubuntu 12.04 &amp;ldquo;Precise Pangolin&amp;rdquo; had a three-year support cycle which concluded on April 26.&#xA;While it will continue to receive updates from the repository, we will no longer be providing any Xubuntu support for packages. Packages provided via Xubuntu-owned PPAs will also be discontinued.&#xA;All users are advised to upgrade their installation to the current LTS, Xubuntu 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/15-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 15:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/15-04-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 15.04 Vivid Vervet The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.04!&#xA;The release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/.&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a complete list of methods to get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.04 Beta 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/xubuntu-15-04-beta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 21:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/xubuntu-15-04-beta-2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.04 Beta 2. This is the final beta towards the release of 15.04 in April.&#xA;Please note the important install known issue at Bug 1436715: &amp;ldquo;Vivid DVD fails to reboot or shutdown w/o hard reset&amp;rdquo;&#xA;If you are at all unsure about a hard reset, the options are&#xA;Install Beta 1 and dist-upgrade Wait for the bug to fix and install from a daily Wait for Release Candidate The Beta 2 release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads fromhttp://cdimage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.04 Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/xubuntu-15-04-beta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 19:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/15.04/xubuntu-15-04-beta-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 15.04 Beta 1. This is the first beta towards the final release in April.&#xA;The first beta release also marks the end of the period to land new features in the form of Ubuntu Feature Freeze. This means any new updates to packages should be bug fixes only, the Xubuntu team is committed to fixing as many of the bugs as possible before the final release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at Mexican collection agencies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-mexican-collection-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 00:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-mexican-collection-agencies/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this “Xubuntu at..” series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you’re doing with us please contact Elizabeth K. Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Late last year we heard from developer Greg Blumenthal when he told us that he&amp;rsquo;d been deploying Xubuntu to customers who were &amp;ldquo;extremely happy&amp;rdquo; with their new systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04.2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-2-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 23:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-2-released/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 14.04 Trusty Tahr The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04.2 Xubuntu 14.04 is an LTS (Long-Term Support) release and will be supported for 3 years. This is the second Point Release of it&amp;rsquo;s cycle.&#xA;The final release images are available as Torrents and direct downloads at http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/14.04.2/release/&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help the Community with testing and win Xubuntu stickers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/help-the-community-with-testing-and-win-xubuntu-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/help-the-community-with-testing-and-win-xubuntu-stickers/</guid>
      <description>Manual testing of the development version is an important part of the development cycle. The goal of manual testing is to find bugs that have been introduced during the cycle.&#xA;Finding these gives developers the opportunity to fix issues before the release. The sooner they are found, the bigger the possibility is that the bugs are fixed before regular users see them on their desktop. Without manual testers, our releases would be buggy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.10 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/14-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 12:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/14-10-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 14.10 Utopic Unicorn The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.10!&#xA;The release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads from http://xubuntu.org/getxubuntu/&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a complete list of methods to get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.10 Beta 2 is released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/xubuntu-14-10-beta-2-is-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 03:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/xubuntu-14-10-beta-2-is-released/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.10 Beta 2. This is the final beta towards the release in October. Before this beta we have landed various of enhancements and some new features. Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to start polishing the last edges and improve the stability. The Beta 2 release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads fromhttp://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/utopic/beta-2/&#xA;Highlights and known issues To celebrate the 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.10 Beta 1 is released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/xubuntu-14-10-beta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 21:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/xubuntu-14-10-beta-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.10 Beta 1. This is the first beta towards the final release in October. Before this beta we have landed various of enhancements and some new features. Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to start polishing the last edges and improve the stability.&#xA;The first beta release also marks the end of the period to land new features in the form of Ubuntu Feature Freeze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using inxi to detect hardware information</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/inxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.10/inxi/</guid>
      <description>inxi is a full featured system information script that will detect information about hardware specifications, including but not limited to vendor details, CPU info, graphic and sound cards. Most importantly, it will output everything in a easy to read format and it can also be used on irc clients like irssi, weechat or xchat.&#xA;How to use inxi? The general use of inxi is inxi -&amp;lt;color&amp;gt; -&amp;lt;option&amp;gt;. inxi output is colored and to change the color for better visibility use the c option followed by a number between 0-32.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptop users: Fix available for the black screen on unlock bug</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/laptop-users-fix-available-for-the-black-screen-on-unlock-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/laptop-users-fix-available-for-the-black-screen-on-unlock-bug/</guid>
      <description>If you experienced problems with logging into your session after suspending your laptop by closing the lid (and only this exact scenario!), your days of worry should be over now. Many users have commented on the respective bugreport, many of whom experienced different issues with suspending. This made the issue very difficult to pinpoint in the beginning for us technical folk and confusing for users too.&#xA;Sean Davis, Technical Lead of Xubuntu, put together the pieces we collected after identifying the issue and the fix landed in the 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things to Do After Upgrading from 12.04 to 14.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/5-things-to-do-after-upgrading-from-12-04-to-14-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 13:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/5-things-to-do-after-upgrading-from-12-04-to-14-04/</guid>
      <description>The first point release of 14.04 just came out a few days ago and many LTS users waited for this to upgrade from 12.04 – in fact do-release-upgrade only offers the LTS to LTS upgrade after the first point release for stability reasons. So we thought this would be the perfect time to do a quick writeup of a few things to do after upgrading your system. User configuration isn&amp;rsquo;t updated and installed applications aren&amp;rsquo;t removed when upgrading and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing: Upgraders will not have to restore their customizations and their system will mostly look as before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04.1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-1-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-1-released/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 14.04 Trusty Tahr The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04.1 Xubuntu 14.04 is an LTS (Long-Term Support) release and will be supported for 3 years. This is the first Point Release of it&amp;rsquo;s cycle.&#xA;The final release images are available as Torrents and direct downloads at http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/trusty/release/&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screen locking in Xubuntu 14.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/screen-locking-in-xubuntu-14-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 11:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/screen-locking-in-xubuntu-14-04/</guid>
      <description>Improving screenlocking (or: sessionlocking) has been on our agenda for a few cycles now. We&amp;rsquo;ve used the old and proven XScreensaver for a few releases, but people have always complained about its antiquated looks (which are also not customizable). Switching to gnome-screensaver wasn&amp;rsquo;t an option because of the additional package dependencies. Furthermore, after gnome-screensaver 3.6, locking became more tightly integrated into Gnome-Shell, which is why Ubuntu/Unity kept version 3.6 and has maintained it for a few releases now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 QA Recap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-qa-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 16:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-qa-recap/</guid>
      <description>Now that Trusty is out the door, we thought that the time was right to bring you a recap of what you&amp;rsquo;ve managed to do for Xubuntu during the last cycle and what we&amp;rsquo;ve been up to behind the curtain. Those of you who frequent the #xubuntu-devel channel are likely aware of how much the work people testing do is appreciated. The remainder of you perhaps don&amp;rsquo;t, or just assume so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/14-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/14-04-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 14.04 Trusty Tahr The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04. Xubuntu 14.04 is an LTS (Long-Term Support) release and will be supported for 3 years.&#xA;The final release images are available as Torrents and direct downloads at http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/14.04/release/&#xA;As the main server will be very busy in the first days after the release, we recommend using the Torrents wherever possible.&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a complete list of methods to get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 Final Beta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-final-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 23:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-final-beta/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04 Beta 2. This is the last beta towards the final LTS release.&#xA;If this is the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve looked at a Beta this cycle then much has changed. Please see the notes from Beta 1 for more details on those.&#xA;The Beta 2 release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads from http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/trusty/beta-2/&#xA;Release notes can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-beta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 18:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-beta-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is pleased to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04 Beta 1. This is the first beta towards the final LTS release, and with it we have landed a lot of new features and improvements we&amp;rsquo;ve been preparing since the last LTS release two years ago.&#xA;The beta 1 release is available for download by torrents and direct downloads from http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/trusty/beta-1/&#xA;Highlights and known issues The highlights of this release include:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Marketing with StartUbuntu Flyer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/xubuntu-marketing-with-startubuntu-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 23:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/xubuntu-marketing-with-startubuntu-flyer/</guid>
      <description>The StartUbuntu project seeks to spread Ubuntu to individuals and organizations who are migrating away from Windows XP when support runs out later this year. As one of their initiatives, Pierre van Male created a flyer featuring Ubuntu and Linux Mate (available here, A4 size only). We decided that this would be a great opportunity to create our own variation - with Xubuntu!&#xA;This month Elizabeth Krumbach Joseph and Pasi Lallinaho got to work on text and graphical updates to make this a reality and we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that the flyers have been created and uploaded to SpreadUbuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporting is caring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/reporting-is-caring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2014/reporting-is-caring/</guid>
      <description>While testing the developer versions in any way possible is a great idea, there isn&amp;rsquo;t much benefit in messages telling us Xubuntu works on machine X, or there were no problems with upgrading machine Y.&#xA;Why? It&amp;rsquo;s not measurable.&#xA;The following sections will explain the kind of figures we would like to measure, why those figures are important and will hopefully give you some motivation to start running and and reporting tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04.4 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/xubuntu-12-04-4-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 19:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/xubuntu-12-04-4-released/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 12.04.4, the last point release for 12.04, has been released today along with the rest of the Ubuntu flavors. Users using Xubuntu 12.04 will be upgraded to 12.04.4 automatically along with normal upgrades.&#xA;The 12.04.4 point release brings in completely updated documentation that is also specifically targeted for 12.04. The complete release notes for this last point release can be found at https://wiki.ubuntu.com/PrecisePangolin/ReleaseNotes/Xubuntu.&#xA;The support window for Xubuntu 12.04 will end on April 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu community wallpaper contest winners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/community-wallpaper-contest-winners/</guid>
      <description>First of all, we&amp;rsquo;d like to thank everyone who contributed to our contest! Thanks for giving us a choice and for making it a really difficult process to distill all submissions down to a set of 6 amazing looking wallpapers.&#xA;As announced at the outset, three members of the Xubuntu development team, namely Pasi Lallinaho (Project Lead), Elizabeth Krumbach (Marketing Lead) and Simon Steinbeiss (Artwork Lead) reviewed the lot of 81 submissions to the contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 Alpha 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-alpha-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 18:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-alpha-2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04 Alpha 2!&#xA;As often expected with very early cycle releases, this release has some issues which we will be working to resolve before the final release.&#xA;Notably, it is impossible to successfully use the Alpha 2 to set up an auto-resized system automatically. You will not be able to set the partition sizes.&#xA;Thanks to the 12 who tested and reported to the tracker for Alpha 2:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 Alpha 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-alpha-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 19:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-alpha-1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 14.04 Alpha 1!&#xA;As often expected with very early cycle releases, this release has some major issues which we will be working to resolve before the final release. The main issues center around the various User Session bugs seen.&#xA;To boot successfully to a Xubuntu Desktop on the Live DVD you need to set the session to Xubuntu at the Gear Icon, Language at the Flag Icon and use username xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help us test Xubuntu 14.04 LTS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/help-us-test-xubuntu-14-04-lts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 22:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/help-us-test-xubuntu-14-04-lts/</guid>
      <description>In less than 6 months time we will release Xubuntu 14.04 Trusty Tahr, a long-term release which will be supported for 3 years. Even if you have never dabbled in testing – now is the time to have a go!&#xA;How can I help? Testing Xubuntu is an important step on the way to the release of a stable operating system. With proper and reported testing we are able to find out the bugs and issues and iron them out before the final release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04 Default Wallpapers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-default-wallpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 20:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/14.04/xubuntu-14-04-default-wallpapers/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce that for 14.04 we plan to integrate a set of good-looking wallpapers by default. This is a feature many have been lacking for a while, we repeatedly heard/read about it in reviews. And we think the upcoming 14.04 LTS release is the perfect time to finally tackle this issue.&#xA;We want the community (yes, you who is reading this!) to participate in this process – so we&amp;rsquo;re looking for your wallpaper submissions!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at Techs for a Cause in Kansas City</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-techs-for-a-cause-in-kansas-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 15:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-techs-for-a-cause-in-kansas-city/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this &amp;ldquo;Xubuntu at..&amp;rdquo; series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you&amp;rsquo;re doing with us please contact Elizabeth Krumbach Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Back in September we heard from Chris Wiley of Techs for a Cause and were put in touch with Justin Henneberg to answer some questions about their organization and how they use Xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 13.10 is released!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 13:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-final/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is delighted to announce the release of Xubuntu 13.10!&#xA;Some of the highlights for Xubuntu 13.10 include:&#xA;A new version of xfce4-settings has been uploaded, bringing amongst other things a new dialog to set up your displays A tool for changing your theme colors easily, gtk-theme-config, has been added to the default installation New wallpaper New releases of our Gtk themes (with Gtk3.10 support) as well as the LightDM greeter, fixing many visual bugs Updated documentation The release notes along with full list of new features and known issues can be found at https://wiki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Saucy Salamander Beta 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 09:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-b2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the release of Xubuntu Saucy Salamander Beta 2! Please note that this beta is not suited for production machines. Always back up your data before upgrading.&#xA;With this beta, we hope to have most of our important features ready as well as most of the critical bugs fixed. The team has worked hard triaging and fixing bugs and we are happy to have been able to ship fixes for many bugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Saucy Salamander Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 21:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/saucy-salamander-b1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to announce the release of Xubuntu 13.10 Saucy Salamander Beta 1 today. Please note that this beta is not intended for use on production computers but for use in testing. Do not think it is &amp;ldquo;close enough&amp;rdquo; to done to be safe for your production machine and always back up your data.&#xA;With this beta, we hope to have all of the most important features ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Xubuntu Desktop Showcase</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/announcing-xubuntu-desktop-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 16:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/announcing-xubuntu-desktop-showcase/</guid>
      <description>Time to reveal your desktop! The Xubuntu team is proud to announce a recently launched new project to celebrate our community: the Xubuntu Showcase group group on deviantART!&#xA;What is the goal of this project? The ultimate goal of this project is to have &amp;ldquo;Desktop of the Week&amp;rdquo; gallery on our website. Each week we will choose a single submission among the pool and showcase it in the front page of the official Xubuntu website as well as promote it on all of our social network outlets and let others do the same!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu at Project: Community Computers in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-project-community-computers-in-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/series/xubuntu-at/xubuntu-at-project-community-computers-in-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team hears stories about how it is used in organizations all over the world. In this &amp;ldquo;Xubuntu at..&amp;rdquo; series of interviews, we seek to interview organizations who wish to share their stories. If your organization is using Xubuntu and you want to share what you&amp;rsquo;re doing with us please contact Elizabeth Krumbach Joseph at lyz@ubuntu.com to discuss details about your organization.&#xA;Jeff Hanson of Project: Community Computers recently contacted the Xubuntu developers to introduce the work his organization is doing and ask about how best to give feedback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu stickers now available</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/xubuntu-stickers-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 16:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/xubuntu-stickers-now-available/</guid>
      <description>We recently teamed up with the folks over at UnixStickers.com to begin offering Xubuntu stickers and case badges for purchase. We&amp;rsquo;re happy to report that they&amp;rsquo;ve now got the designs up and are available for shipment worldwide.&#xA;To buy the Xubuntu stickers right now, navigate to the Xubuntu sticker collection homepage on UnixStickers.com.&#xA;Various styles are available, including Xubuntu logo white on blue rounded shaped sticker (top left), Xubuntu mouse w/logotype black on white shaped sticker (bottom) and Xubuntu OS badge sticker (top right):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking towards Xubuntu 13.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/looking-towards-xubuntu-13-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 23:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.10/looking-towards-xubuntu-13-10/</guid>
      <description>After three Nights of Xubuntu, the Xubuntu team is able to present you a quick overview of some of the planned features and improvements for Xubuntu 13.10. Enjoy!&#xA;Software and development On the software side, apt-offline will be included in our default installation after a few cycles of preparing and writing documentation for it. This will help our users who have impaired-bandwidth situations and usage documentation is already present in the 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booting the Xubuntu USB image from a CD</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/booting-the-xubuntu-usb-image-from-a-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 09:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2013/booting-the-xubuntu-usb-image-from-a-cd/</guid>
      <description>Due to the size of the Xubuntu ISOs starting from Raring (13.04), they no longer fit on a standard CD. This guide will help you if your BIOS doesn&amp;rsquo;t support booting off of USB drives by showing you how to use Plop boot manager.&#xA;Getting Plop You can download the most recent version here (plpbt-*).&#xA;Executing Plop The burning process is similar as documented on the Ubuntu wiki.&#xA;Main contents of the downloaded archive should be:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 13.04 is here!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/13-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 12:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/13-04-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 13.04!&#xA;Xubuntu 13.04 will be supported for 9 months and will need other media such as a USB device or a DVD to install. Read more below.&#xA;Download Xubuntu 13.04 here!&#xA;What&amp;rsquo;s new in Xubuntu 13.04? Xubuntu 13.04 is mostly a maintenance release, and there aren&amp;rsquo;t many new features. However, there are some changes, which include:&#xA;Gnumeric and GIMP are reintroduced on the ISO New application versions: Catfish 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Beta 2 is out!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/raring-beta2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 13:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/raring-beta2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 13.04 Beta 2!&#xA;Note: Starting from 13.04, the Xubuntu images will not fit on standard CDs any more. This affects the Beta 2 images as well. To install Xubuntu you will need other media such as a USB device or a DVD. The Xubuntu 13.04 Beta 2 image size is approximately 800 MB.&#xA;Xubuntu 13.04 is mostly a maintenance release, and there won&amp;rsquo;t be too many new features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Xubuntu 13.04 Beta 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/raring-beta1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 20:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/raring-beta1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 13.04 Beta 1!&#xA;Note: Starting from 13.04, the Xubuntu images will not fit on standard CDs any more. This affects the Beta 1 images as well. To install Xubuntu, you will need other media such as a USB device or a DVD. The Xubuntu 13.04 Beta 1 image size is approximately 850 MB.&#xA;Xubuntu 13.04 is mostly a maintenance release, and there won&amp;rsquo;t be too many new features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to help out Xubuntu? Test Raring!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/want-to-help-out-xubuntu-test-raring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 23:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/want-to-help-out-xubuntu-test-raring/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s again the time to call for more testers – Xubuntu Raring beta 1 is around.&#xA;Why help with testing? Testing is an excellent and easy way to get involved with Xubuntu. It’s a vital part of our release cycle and anyone with a virtual machine (or even better, a spare computer!) can help out with it. When you do testing you will work with most of the people involved in Xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu goes 1GB for Raring, GIMP and Gnumeric are back</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/xubuntu-goes-1gb-for-raring-gimp-and-gnumeric-are-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 17:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/13.04/xubuntu-goes-1gb-for-raring-gimp-and-gnumeric-are-back/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team had an extra meeting on Monday to discuss and decide a possible move to a bigger ISO size and other important issues for Raring.&#xA;After a thorough discussion, which included the obvious drawback that will no longer fit on a CD and the amount of developer time currently spent keeping the ISO small enough to fit on a CD, the team decided that Xubuntu will have a 1GB ISO by clear vote of 8-0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ for Xubuntu 12.10 Quantal Quetzal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/faq-1210-quantal-quetzal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/faq-1210-quantal-quetzal/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! To provide a better experience to all the Xubuntu users we gather what we consider to be common questions any user might come to find.&#xA;We have been doing this for the last few releases, check the previous FAQ to find out interesting and probably helpful information about your system.&#xA;In this particular release of Xubuntu we have moved out of Xfce 4.8, into the most recent 4.10, this carries some issues when updating that we would like to help you overcome:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.10 is out!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/12-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/12-10-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 12.10, codenamed Quantal Quetzal! Xubuntu 12.10 will be supported for 18 months.&#xA;Download Xubuntu 12.10 here!&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a full listing of methods to get help.&#xA;To see the complete release notes along with list of updates and issues in common infrastructure and more, please refer to the Xubuntu release notes at the Ubuntu wiki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Xubuntu 12.10 Beta 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalbeta2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalbeta2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is glad to announce the immediate release of Xubuntu 12.10 Beta 2!&#xA;Along with new features and completely new looks, Beta 2 comes with other changes too: the Xubuntu team has decided to drop the alternate images at least for 12.10 due to the lack of manpower.&#xA;New features include:&#xA;Updated artwork, including new wallpaper, documentation looks and updates to LightDM, Greybird and Ubiquity slideshow Completely reviewed and rewritten offline documentation New versions of Catfish and Parole Notable bug fixes include:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline documentation rewritten for 12.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/offline-documentation-rewritten-for-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/offline-documentation-rewritten-for-12-10/</guid>
      <description>When you go to &amp;ldquo;Help&amp;rdquo; in the main menu in Xubuntu Firefox will launch and bring you to an offline documentation page where users can learn the basics.&#xA;After a couple of cycles without updates, the Xubuntu team worked hard this cycle to take a fresh look at the documentation. The team spent time reorganizing the structure, updating to reflect current default applications and in many cases completely rewriting whole sections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Quantal Beta 1 for Xubuntu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/no-quantal-beta-1-for-xubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 23:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/no-quantal-beta-1-for-xubuntu/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed in the release announcement for Beta 1 today from Kate Stewart this line:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;With Ubuntu 12.10, Kubuntu, Edubuntu, Lubuntu, and Ubuntu Studio also reached Beta 1 status today. These images, along with Xubuntu will continue to have daily updates for the remainder of the release.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;You read right, Xubuntu didn&amp;rsquo;t release a Beta 1 this time around but we are continuing to work on our daily builds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTS upgrade time!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/12-04-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 19:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/12-04-1-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 12.04.1 has been released today along with the rest of the Ubuntu flavors. This means everybody on 10.04 are able to upgrade to 12.04.1 at their convenience. Users on 10.04 should get an upgrade notification when booting their systems up the next time.&#xA;Users using Xubuntu 12.04 will be upgraded to 12.04.1 automatically along with normal upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.10 alpha 3 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalalpha3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 21:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalalpha3/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is proud to announce the Alpha3 release of Xubuntu 12.10, Quantal Quetzal!&#xA;We don&amp;rsquo;t have any major changes from the Alpha2, but there are a few known issues you should be aware of:&#xA;There are no alternate images for this release The image is still oversized for 700M CDs (see related bugs: 1028486, 1029552), please use a USB stick, DVD or other method for installing these oversized images All applications using Gtk3 currently have some mismatched colors in menus and buttons because of a bug in the Unico engine (1016713).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Xubuntu social media admins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2012/thank-you-xubuntu-social-media-admins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 02:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2012/thank-you-xubuntu-social-media-admins/</guid>
      <description>In the past year the Xubuntu project has gone from zero to four social media outlets for sharing our project updates, news and discussions. All of these resources are linked at the bottom of every page on Xubuntu.org.&#xA;The most exceptional thing about this experience is that not only did three of the four outlets already exist as fan-created sites, all three of these admins where delighted to add a member of the Xubuntu leadership team as an admin and have their page made Official by the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.10 alpha 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalalpha2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 12:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/quantalalpha2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is proud to announce the Alpha2 release of Xubuntu 12.10, Quantal Quetzal!&#xA;Updates for this release include Xfce 4.10 Updated applications, including GIMP 2.8 and gThumb 3.0.1 In addition, starting from the Quantal cycle, Xubuntu will not support Wubi installations.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers – see the ISO testing tracker. Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu&#39;s default theme gets a refresh for Quantal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/xubuntus-default-theme-gets-a-refresh-for-quantal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 11:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/xubuntus-default-theme-gets-a-refresh-for-quantal/</guid>
      <description>While we&amp;rsquo;ve been using &amp;ldquo;Greybird&amp;rdquo; as our default theme for a few releases now, I&amp;rsquo;ve continuously worked on it. The goal was not only to ensure the quality of the theme in terms of a flawless Xfce4 and Gtk3 performance and extras like supporting Unity or Compiz, but also to visually keep it up-to-date.&#xA;More contrast After having had a tendency to soften colors and contrasts, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to take a (bold?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brainstorming the 12.10 release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/brainstorming-the-12-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 23:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/brainstorming-the-12-10-release/</guid>
      <description>It is the time to submit your ideas on how to make Xubuntu better: the brainstorming phase for the 12.10 roadmap is on now! It is also a good time to start contributing, since every item needs an assignee – without assignees, even good ideas will not be approved – thus not implemented.&#xA;Everybody is welcome to submit ideas to the roadmap brainstorm until the end of week 19 (13th of May).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ for Xubuntu 12.04 Precise Pangolin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/faq-1204-precise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 17:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/faq-1204-precise/</guid>
      <description>1. Is there a way to use folders shared from Windows? Yes, using Gigolo. If you are not able to see the network check if gvfs-backends is installed.&#xA;2. Thunar loads very slowly on first launch, how do I fix that? Unfortunately, this is a known bug. There are two possible solutions:&#xA;Edit the file /usr/share/gvfs/mounts/network.mount (as root) and change AutoMount to false. This disables the Network browsing when Thunar starts up, but still lets you mount network storage such as Samba shares on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/12-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/12-04-release/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is very proud and happy to announce the release of Xubuntu 12.04, codenamed Precise Pangolin! Xubuntu 12.04 is a Long Term Support release (LTS) and will be supported for three years per the Xubuntu LTS plan.&#xA;Download Xubuntu 12.04 here&#xA;For support with the release, navigate to Help &amp;amp; Support for a full listing of methods to get help.&#xA;To see the complete release notes along with list of updates and issues in common infrastructure and more, please refer to the Xubuntu release notes at the Ubuntu wiki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Artwork Update: Unity Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/xubuntu-artwork-update-unity-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 17:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.10/xubuntu-artwork-update-unity-support/</guid>
      <description>While there are many people who project a competition between Ubuntu and its flavors, I&amp;rsquo;d like to set a (small) sign that this is definitely not the case.&#xA;With respect to our default theme, &amp;ldquo;Greybird&amp;rdquo;, I have been striving to expand the supported window-managers in the last release &amp;ldquo;Oneiric Ocelot, 11.10&amp;rdquo; (metacity, emerald), to give people who want to use Compiz in Xubuntu an easy way to use our default look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Window resizing in Xubuntu (and Xfce)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/window-resizing-in-xubuntu-and-xfce/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/window-resizing-in-xubuntu-and-xfce/</guid>
      <description>For quite a while now there has been questions about resizing windows in Xfce, especially with theme with narrow window-borders. Usually people would ask for wider window-borders, but there are several methods of resizing a window and the thin borders in Xubuntu&amp;rsquo;s current default theme Greybird are not as much of a usability issue as some suggest.&#xA;The five methods Method 1: Using the resize grip Resize grips (usually small triangles) are positioned in the bottom right corner of a window, often as part of a statusbar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Countdown is on</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/the-countdown-is-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 07:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/the-countdown-is-on/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s already less than a month before Xubuntu 12.04 is released, and we thought it would be a good thing to finally provide you something to build up the excitement (and hype) with. So here it is&amp;hellip;&#xA;Countdown banners for Xubuntu 12.04 The &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo;, legacy-sized banner:&#xA;&amp;hellip;and the alternative, wide version:&#xA;How to add these to my site? You only need a short snippet of code:&#xA;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;ldquo;http://xubuntu.org/&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;ldquo;http://xubuntu.org/countdown/&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;Countdown to Xubuntu 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beta 2 released &amp; new branding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/beta-2-released-new-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/beta-2-released-new-branding/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is proud to announce the Beta2 release of Xubuntu 12.04, Precise Pangolin!&#xA;Updates for this release include The i386 images use a non-PAE kernel to support a bigger variety of machines Pavucontrol is now used over xfce4-mixer Some default shortcuts have been changed and some added, see https://wiki.ubuntu.com/Xubuntu/Roadmap/Specifications/Precise/DefaultShortcutKeys#Detailed_specification for the complete list Lots of appearance tweaks and improvements, including fixes for Ubiquity, Plymouth and the Greybird theme New branding Try it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help test Xubuntu!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/help-test-xubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 15:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/help-test-xubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu Beta 2 is coming out this week and we need testers!&#xA;Testing is an excellent way to get involved with Xubuntu. It&amp;rsquo;s a vital part of our release cycle and anyone with a virtual machine (or even better, a spare computer!) can help out with it.&#xA;The Xubuntu community maintains extensive documents related to testing, we highly recommend you browse through these as you get more involved with testing:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04 beta 1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/precisebeta1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/precisebeta1/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is proud to announce the Beta1 release of Xubuntu 12.04, Precise Pangolin!&#xA;Updates for this release include Using new maybe-ubiquity greeter Alacarte is seeded by default in Xubuntu Precise beta, and will show all Xfce-related menu items on Xubuntu as well. Some default shortcuts have been changed and some added, see DefaultShortcutKeys for the complete list New wallpaper and other tweaks and improvements to the looks of Xubuntu are in, including lots of GTK3 fixes for the Greybird theme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing our web presence to 2012</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2012/webpresence2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 17:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2012/webpresence2012/</guid>
      <description>After a long, long wait and much hard work, we are ready to proudly present the new Xubuntu website!&#xA;New looks The appearance is updated and more sleek, clean, professional, informative, beautiful and representative. It&amp;rsquo;s easier to navigate on the site. The header area is less obtrusive. Generally speaking, you get faster to the content. We are also finally using our new branding.&#xA;The long-awaited migration We&amp;rsquo;ve switched from Drupal to WordPress under the hood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04 alpha 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/precisealpha2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/12.04/precisealpha2/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is proud to announce the Alpha2 release of Xubuntu 12.04, Precise Pangolin!&#xA;Updates for this release include New greeter + theme xfdesktop4 has been updated to support single click to open items, thumbnail support for the desktop. xfce4-settings has been updated to include the new mouche/touchpad dialog (backported from 4.9.x) Some other syncs, updates and patches from Debian and upstream, including: xfce4-power-manager, Ristretto and gmusicbrowser Minor updates to default settings and packages, mostly appearance (including Terminal font size change) Visit the download page to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ for Xubuntu 11.10 Oneiric Ocelot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/faq-1110-oneiric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 22:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/faq-1110-oneiric/</guid>
      <description>1. I can’t hear a sound. How can I get my sound back? There are many reasons why sound can be lost on a system, most of them if you try to use different audio protocols. The usual way to get sound back is to run sudo /etc/init.d/alsa-utils restart.&#xA;If this doesn’t work you can try running sudo alsa force-unload and sudo alsa force-reload.&#xA;Pulseaudio can sometimes cause conflicts with ALSA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.10 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/11-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 05:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/11-10-release/</guid>
      <description>There are a few times when, through hard work and diligence, we get things right. The developers and contributors of Xubuntu 11.10 “Oneiric Ocelot” believe they have it right. They are proud to announce the release of Xubuntu 11.10, &amp;ldquo;Oneiric Ocelot&amp;rdquo;. Through the outstanding efforts of all involved, this sleek and smooth release offered for your enjoyment and use.&#xA;Changes for this release include the following applications included by default: gThumb, pastebinit, and onboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Oneiric Ocelot beta2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricbeta2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricbeta2/</guid>
      <description>There are a few times when, through hard work and diligence, we get things right. The developers and contributors of Xubuntu 11.10 “Oneiric Ocelot” believe they have it right. They are proud to announce the second beta release of Xubuntu 11.10 &amp;ldquo;Oneiric Ocelot&amp;rdquo;. This is still a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. Please do not install Oneiric Ocelot Beta2 on your production system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Oneiric Ocelot beta1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricbeta1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 13:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricbeta1/</guid>
      <description>The first beta release of Xubuntu 11.10 &amp;ldquo;Oneiric Ocelot&amp;rdquo; has arrived. The developers are working hard to make Xubuntu 11.10 one of the best Linux distributions yet. They are striving to ensure that everything will work for all users, and instead of many changes, are working to ensure the release is very stable and secure.&#xA;This is still a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.10 alpha 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricalpha2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 08:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.10/oneiricalpha2/</guid>
      <description>Another great milestone reached: Xubuntu 11.10 Oneiric Ocelot Alpha 2 released&#xA;The second alpha release of Xubuntu 11.10 &amp;ldquo;Oneiric Ocelot&amp;rdquo; has arrived. The developers are working hard to make Xubuntu 11.10 one of the best Linux distributions yet. They are striving to ensure that everything will work for all users, and instead of many changes, are working to ensure the release is very stable and secure.&#xA;This is still a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/11-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/11-04-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 11.04, codenamed the &amp;ldquo;Natty Narwhal&amp;rdquo;, is the latest and greatest version of Xubuntu, released on April 28th, 2011. Building on the success of Xubuntu 10.10, Xubuntu 11.04 looks forward to continuing the tradition of being a light-weight and easy-to-use Linux distribution built on top of the high-quality and feature-rich core of Ubuntu.&#xA;Release Notes To learn about all the great enhancements and improvements that can be found in Xubuntu 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04 beta 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattybeta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 15:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattybeta-2/</guid>
      <description>The second and final beta release of Xubuntu 11.04 &amp;ldquo;Natty Narwhal&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for testers and developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. This beta replaces the traditional Release Candidate - the stable version for end-users will be released April 28th 2011, so these last two weeks of testing are of utmost importance for a stable release.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04 beta 1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattybeta-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattybeta-1/</guid>
      <description>The first beta release of Xubuntu 11.04 &amp;ldquo;Natty Narwhal&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. The second beta will be released April 14th, and will replace the traditional Release Candidate.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu Natty Artwork</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/natty-artwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 09:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/natty-artwork/</guid>
      <description>As one of Xubuntu&amp;rsquo;s artwork contributors and member of the Shimmerproject I would like to take some time now - towards the end of this cycle - and discuss (at least parts of) the design process during the development phase for Natty (11.04). This is planned as a review and in a way (implicitely) a preview: you can see the direction Xubuntu is heading for since Maverick and Natty and hopefully the project will continue this way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04 alpha 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattyalpha-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 14:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattyalpha-2/</guid>
      <description>The second alpha release of Xubuntu 11.04 &amp;ldquo;Natty Narwhal&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker. Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.&#xA;If you are looking for support), please see the #ubuntu+1 or #xubuntu IRC channels on irc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04 alpha 1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattyalpha-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/11.04/nattyalpha-1/</guid>
      <description>The first alpha release of Xubuntu 11.04 &amp;ldquo;Natty Narwhal&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker. Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.&#xA;If you are looking for support), please see the #ubuntu+1 or #xubuntu IRC channels on irc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.10 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/10-10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 12:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/10-10-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 10.10, codenamed the &amp;ldquo;Maverick Meerkat&amp;rdquo;, is the latest and greatest version of Xubuntu, released on October 10th, 2010. Building on the success of Xubuntu 10.04, Xubuntu 10.10 looks forward to continuing the tradition of being a light-weight and easy-to-use Linux distribution built on top of the high-quality and feature-rich core of Ubuntu.&#xA;Release Notes To learn about all the great enhancements and improvements that can be found in Xubuntu 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.10 RC released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 13:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickrc/</guid>
      <description>The release candidate of Xubuntu 10.10 &amp;ldquo;Maverick Meerkat&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in this RC release, please see the notes on Xubuntu in the Ubuntu Release Notes.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.10 alpha 3 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickalpha-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 08:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickalpha-3/</guid>
      <description>The third alpha release of Xubuntu 10.10 &amp;ldquo;Maverick Meerkat&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker. Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.&#xA;If you are looking for support), please see the #ubuntu+1 or #xubuntu IRC channels on irc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.10 alpha 1 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickalpha-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.10/maverickalpha-1/</guid>
      <description>The first alpha release of Xubuntu 10.10 &amp;ldquo;Maverick Meerkat&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker, Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.&#xA;If you are looking for support), please see the #ubuntu+1 or #xubuntu IRC channels on irc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.04 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.04/10-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 10:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.04/10-04-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 10.04, codenamed the &amp;ldquo;Lucid Lynx&amp;rdquo;, is the latest and greatest version of Xubuntu, released on April 29th, 2010. Building on the success of Xubuntu 9.10, Xubuntu 10.04 looks forward to continuing the tradition of being a light-weight and easy-to-use Linux distribution built on top of the high-quality and feature-rich core of Ubuntu.&#xA;Release Notes To learn about all the great enhancements and improvements that can be found in Xubuntu 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.04 beta 2 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.04/lucidbeta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/10.04/lucidbeta-2/</guid>
      <description>The second beta release of Xubuntu 10.04 &amp;ldquo;Lucid Lynx&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in the beta release, please see the Release Notes.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker, Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.10 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/9-10-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 05:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/9-10-released/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 9.10, codenamed the &amp;ldquo;Karmic Koala&amp;rdquo;, is the latest and greatest version of Xubuntu, released on October 29th, 2009. It integrates the latest Xfce-desktop releases with the high-quality and feature-rich core of Ubuntu, resulting in a light-weight and easy-to-use Linux distribution.&#xA;Release Notes To learn about all the great enhancements and improvements that can be found in Xubuntu 9.10, please see the release notes.&#xA;Download Get it while it&amp;rsquo;s hot. ISOs and torrents are available at:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.10 RC released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/karmicrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 02:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/karmicrc/</guid>
      <description>The release candidate of Xubuntu 9.10 &amp;ldquo;Karmic Koala&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in this RC release, please see the Release Notes.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker, Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.10 beta released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/karmicbeta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 04:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.10/karmicbeta/</guid>
      <description>The beta has now been superseded by the release candidate, links on this page will not work.&#xA;The beta of Xubuntu 9.10 &amp;ldquo;Karmic Koala&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in the beta release, please see the Release Notes.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Xubuntu CDs now available</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2009/quickship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 11:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2009/quickship/</guid>
      <description>It is now possible to order free Xubuntu CDs (see the Get Xubuntu-page). These CDs are generously provided free of charge by On-Disk.com as part of their Quick Ship free disc service, providing an alternative to Ubuntu&amp;rsquo;s ShipIt service which does not provide Xubuntu. This means potential users only have to pay shipping costs, avoiding having to download Xubuntu over a slow internet connection.&#xA;This entails an independent third party service, not run by Canonical nor the Xubuntu developers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.04 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/9-04-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/9-04-release/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 9.04, codenamed the &amp;ldquo;Jaunty Jackalope&amp;rdquo;, is the latest and greatest version of Xubuntu, released on April 23, 2009. It integrates the latest Xfce-desktop releases with the high-quality and feature-rich core of Ubuntu, resulting in a light-weight and easy-to-use Linux distribution.&#xA;For Ubuntu see http://www.ubuntu.com/news/ubuntu-9.04-desktop For Kubuntu see http://kubuntu.org/news/9.04-release&#xA;Release Notes To learn about all the great enhancements and improvements that can be found in Xubuntu 9.04, please see the release notes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countdown to Xubuntu 9.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/jauntycountdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 10:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/jauntycountdown/</guid>
      <description>As we are approaching the release of Xubuntu 9.04 (code name &amp;ldquo;Jaunty Jackalope&amp;rdquo;), the Xubuntu Team is providing a countdown banner for anyone who wants to get the word spread.&#xA;If you manage a website, blog or any other place of your own on the internet, you can help! Just copy the HTML code below to your website to include a countdown graphic.&#xA;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://xubuntu.org/&amp;quot; title=&amp;quot;Learn more about Xubuntu...&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;http://xubuntu.org/xubuntu-static/jaunty-countdown/&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Countdown to Xubuntu (xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.04 beta released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/jauntybeta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 06:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/9.04/jauntybeta/</guid>
      <description>The Release Candidate of Xubuntu 9.04 &amp;ldquo;Jaunty Jackalope&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in the beta release, please see the Release Announcement.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker, Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 8.10 released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidrelease/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 02:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidrelease/</guid>
      <description>The Xubuntu team is happy to bring you the latest and greatest software the open source community has to offer. This is their latest result: Xubuntu 8.10, which brings a host of excellent improvements built on the rock solid Xfce 4.4.2 desktop environment.&#xA;For Ubuntu see http://www.ubuntu.com/news/ubuntu-8.10-desktop For Kubuntu see https://wiki.kubuntu.org/IntrepidIbex/Kubuntu&#xA;Download Get it while it&amp;rsquo;s hot. ISOs and torrents are available at:&#xA;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/8.10/ (Xubuntu) http://releases.ubuntu.com/releases/8.10 (Ubuntu) http://releases.ubuntu.com/releases/edubuntu/8.10 (Edubuntu add-on) http://releases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 8.10 Release Candidate now available</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidrc/</guid>
      <description>The Release Candidate of Xubuntu 8.10 &amp;ldquo;Intrepid Ibex&amp;rdquo; has arrived. This is a testing build designed for developers and is not suggested for anyone looking for a stable system. If you would like to see what is new in the beta release, please see the Release Notes.&#xA;Visit the download page to give it a try. Be sure to report your testing results to help the Xubuntu developers - see the ISO testing tracker, Bugs can be reported in Launchpad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countdown to Xubuntu 8.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidcountdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/releases/8.10/intrepidcountdown/</guid>
      <description>In preparation for the release of Xubuntu 8.10 (code name &amp;ldquo;Intrepid Ibex&amp;rdquo;), the Xubuntu Team would like to get the word out that this release is coming.&#xA;If you manage a website, blog or any other place of your own on the internet, you can help! Just copy the HTML code below to your website to include a countdown graphic.&#xA;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://xubuntu.org&amp;quot; title=&amp;quot;Learn more about Xubuntu...&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;http://xubuntu.org/xubuntu-static/intrepid-countdown/index.php&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Countdown to Xubuntu (xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/10.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/10.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 10.04 (Lucid) Beta 1 Screenshots Tour by Web Upd8 Xubuntu 10.04 Lucid Lynx Test Review part 1 by Total OS Today Xubuntu 10.04 Lucid Lynx Test Review part 2 by Total OS Today Xubuntu 10.04 Review And First Impressions by UbuntuHelpGuy Xubuntu Linux 10.04 by Desktop Linux Reviews </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/10.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/10.10/</guid>
      <description> Quick Look: Xubuntu 10.10 by Eye On Linux The Meerkat Is Here… A Review of Xubuntu 10.10 by Musings of a Beardy Gnome </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/11.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/11.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 11.04 Natty Narwhal: ein Einblick (German) by burlis Blog Xubuntu 11.04 – Review and First Look. by Blog on Linux and technology Xubuntu 11.04: Solid, Sleek, and Speedy by Linux.com In Other Languages Xubuntu Unity (German) by burlis Blog </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/11.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/11.10/</guid>
      <description> Smooth switch to open source at mental health care provider Rotterdam by European Commission Joinup Ubuntu Alternatives, Xfce, &amp;amp; Having A Go With Fedora 16! by Ainer.org XFCE: Your Lightweight, Speedy, Fully-Fledged Linux by MakeUseOf.com Xubuntu 11.10 and my Netbook by Linux Journal Xubuntu 11.10 Review by Linux Library Xubuntu 11.10. It Came To Stay by Linux notes from DarkDuck Xubuntu 11.10: Unbelievable Easyness of Humanity by Linux notes from DarkDuck </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/12.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/12.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 12.04 LTS Released by Sean Davis Xubuntu 12.04 LTS Review by Gnuman.com Xubuntu 12.04 LTS Review: Perfect Alternative for Those Who Can’t Stand Unity/GNOME Shell by Tech Drive-in Xubuntu 12.04 LTS Screenshot Tour by Softpedia Xubuntu 12.04 review – A most pleasant surprise by Dedoimedo.com Xubuntu 12.04: don’t fix what is not broken by Linux notes from DarkDuck </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/12.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/12.10/</guid>
      <description>The Perfect Desktop – Xubuntu 12.10 (Quantal Quetzal) by falko of HowtoForge Xubuntu 12.10 Arrives in Style by Sean Michael Davis Xubuntu 12.10 Is Available for Download [Screenshot Tour] by Softpedia Xubuntu 12.10 Released With Xfce 4.10 by WebUpd8 Xubuntu 12.10 Review by Gnuman.com Xubuntu 12.10 review – Very nice by Dedoimedo.com Xubuntu 12.10 Review: A shinnier and more attractive desktop! by Arindam Sen of [Linuxed – Exploring Linux distros](Linuxed – Exploring Linux distros) Xubuntu 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/13.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/13.04/</guid>
      <description> Distro Review: Xubuntu 13.04 Raring Ringtail by Linerd of Tux Tweaks Review of Xubuntu 13.04 by Trench Reynolds What’s new in Xubuntu 13.04 by Linuxaria.com Xubuntu 13.04 Available for Download – Quick Overview [Screenshots, Video] by WebUpd8 Xubuntu 13.04 review – Et tu, Brute? by Dedoimedo.com Xubuntu 13.04 Screenshot Tour by Softpedia Xubuntu 13.04 “Raring Ringtail” Review: Rock solid and stable as ever! by Linuxed </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/13.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/13.10/</guid>
      <description> And the best distro of 2013 is… by Dedoimedo.com Xubuntu 13.10 is quite brilliant by Dedoimedo.com Xubuntu 13.10 review – good as always by Silver Moon of Binary Tides Xubuntu 13.10 Screenshot Tour by Softpedia Xubuntu 13.10 “Saucy Salamander” Review: As good as ever! by Arindam Sen of Linuxed </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/14.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/14.04/</guid>
      <description>Asus eeePC still boldly marches on – with Xubuntu 14.04 by Dedoimedo Xubuntu 14.04 LTS by Jim Lynch of Desktop Linux Reviews Xubuntu 14.04 LTS (Trusty Tahr) Is Out and Available for Download by Softpedia Xubuntu 14.04 LTS Trusty Tahr : Video Review and Screenshot Tour by ncode of Ubuntu Portal Xubuntu 14.04 LTS “Trusty Tahr” Review: Buttery smooth and lightweight by Arindam Sen of Linuxed Xubuntu 14.04 Released by Delightedly Linux Xubuntu 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/14.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/14.10/</guid>
      <description> An Everyday Linux User Review Of Xubuntu 14.10 by Gary Newell of [Everyday Linux User](Everyday Linux User) Best Xfce distro of 2014 by Igor Ljubuncic aka Dedoimedo of Netrunner MAG Xubuntu 14.10 by Marius Nestor of Softpedia Xubuntu 14.10 Utopic Unicorn : Fast and Responsive by ncode of Ubuntu Portal Xubuntu 14.10 Utopic Unicorn – Quite brilliant by Dedoimedo Xubuntu 14.10 “Utopic Unicorn” Review: Looks great but slightly disappointed with performance by Arindam Sen of Linuxed </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/15.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/15.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 15.04 Vivid Vervet – Fabulous by Dedoimedo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/16.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/16.04/</guid>
      <description>A Definitive Guide to Install Xubuntu 16.04 LTS by Pradeep Kumar of LinuxTechi A Down and Dirty Look at Xubuntu 16.04 by Christine Hall of FOSS Force A Quick Look At the Xubuntu 16.04 LTS – Feature Tour by Arindam of DebugPoint.com Asus eeePC + Xubuntu 16.04 - Engage! by Dedoimedo Xubuntu 16.04 LTS and Lubuntu 16.04 LTS Released, Get Three Years of Support by Marius Nestor of Softpedia Xubuntu 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/16.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/16.10/</guid>
      <description> An Everyday Linux User Review Of Xubuntu 16.10 - A Good Place To Start by Gary Newell of Everyday Linux User Xubuntu 16.10 Released, Includes Xfce Packages Built with GTK+ 3 Technologies by Marius Nestor of Softpedia Xubuntu 16.10 Yakkety Yak - A breath of fresh air by Dedoimedo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/17.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/17.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 17.04 Zesty Zorro - Vigorous by Dedoimedo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/18.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/18.04/</guid>
      <description>Install Xfce Desktop on Ubuntu and Turn it Into Xubuntu by It&amp;rsquo;s FOSS Lubuntu Vs. Xubuntu by Mohd Sohail of LinuxAndUbuntu Newly Installed Xubuntu 18.04 by Robin Arnaud Review: Galago Pro from System 76 and Xubuntu 18.04 — Bionic Beaver by Victor Forberger of Linux Attorney Starting Up With Xubuntu by Mohd Sohail of LinuxAndUbuntu Xubuntu 18.04 Bionic Beaver - Middle ground by Dedoimedo Xubuntu 18.04 LTS Brings a Revamped Xfce Desktop Experience with New MATE Apps by Marius Nestor of Softpedia [Video] A Look at Xubuntu 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/19.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/19.04/</guid>
      <description>Benchmarked: The Most Power-Efficient Ubuntu 19.04 Flavor Will Surprise You by Jason Evangelho of Forbes Full Circle Magazine, Issue 147, Page 47, Xubuntu 19.04 by Adam Hunt of Full Circle Magazine Xubuntu 19.04 Disco Dingo - A dawn of a renaissance? by Dedoimedo Xubuntu 19.04 Drops Support for 32-Bit Systems, Ships with Xfce 4.13.3 Desktop by Marius Nestor of Softpedia Xubuntu 19.04 Is Ready With To Provide Its Updated Lightweight Xfce Desktop Experience by Phoronix [Video] Thoughts on Xubuntu 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/19.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/19.10/</guid>
      <description>DistroWatch Weekly, Issue 838, Xubuntu 19.10 Review by Jesse Smith of DistroWatch Full Circle Magazine, Issue 151, Page 41, Xubuntu 19.10 by Adam Hunt of Full Circle Magazine These Xfce Versus KDE Numbers Reveal A Shocking Surprise About Linux Desktop Environments by Jason Evangelho of Forbes Ubuntu 19.10 Flavours Released, Now Available to Download by OMG Ubuntu Ubuntu family 19.10 compared. Kubuntu, Ubuntu, Lubuntu, Xubuntu, and Ubuntu-Mate by Low Tech Linux Xubuntu 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/20.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/20.04/</guid>
      <description>A Preview Of Six Flavors Of Ubuntu 20.04 ”Focal Fossa” by DistroTube Distro Hopped Again - Hello Xubuntu and XFCE DistroWatch Weekly, Issue 859, News: Xubuntu presents Testing Week by Jesse Smith of DistroWatch DistroWatch Weekly, Issue 864: Xubuntu 20.04 by Jeff Siegel of Download Xubuntu 20.04 LTS by Juniya of Ubuntu Free How To Set Up a Remote Desktop with X2Go on Ubuntu 20.04 How To Setup The Perfect Linux Workstation With Xubuntu 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/20.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/20.10/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 20.10 Groovy Gorilla review by Dedoimedo In Other Languages [Spanish] Las principales novedades en Xubuntu 20.10 &amp;lsquo;Groovy Gorilla&amp;rsquo; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/21.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/21.04/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu 21.04 Flavours Released, This is What’s New by OMG Ubuntu Ubuntu 21.04 Official flavors are released! This is what is new by Baytecka dot Com Ubuntu 21.04 Official Flavors Bring Latest Desktop Tech. by Debug Point Ubuntu 21.04 Official Flavors Released, Here’s What’s New by 9 to 5 Linux Xubuntu 21.04 Hirsute Hippo screenshots by Open Source Feed Xubuntu 21.04 Progress Update by Blue Sabre Xubuntu 21.04 Review by Distrocrunch [Video] Xubuntu 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/24.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/24.04/</guid>
      <description> First Look: XUBUNTU 24.04 LTS &amp;ldquo;Noble Numbat&amp;rdquo; (STABLE) by 9to5Linux Xubuntu 24.04 LTS overview | elegance and ease of use. by Riba Linux </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/6.06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/6.06/</guid>
      <description> Installing Xubuntu 6.06 on a Gateway Laptop by linux.gotfoo.org Meet The Newest Member of the Ubuntu Family: Introducing Xubuntu by O’Reilly Linux DevCenter Blog Quick Look: Xubuntu Beta 2 by free-bees.co.uk Review of Xubuntu 6.06 Beta (Dapper Drake) by x64bit.net forums Setting Up Xubuntu: The First 20 Minutes by linux.gotfoo.org Trying Xubuntu 6.06 by ddaa bbloggs Xubuntu 6.06 by free-bees.co.uk Xubuntu v6.06 Dapper Drake Beta 2 by Phoronix In Other Languages [German] Ausblick: Xubuntu Dapper Drake Gimicks by ubuntuusers </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/6.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/6.10/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu Gets Edgy by O’Reilly Linux DevCenter Blog </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/7.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/7.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu Gets Feisty by O’Reilly Linux DevCenter Blog </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/7.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/7.10/</guid>
      <description> A peek at the Xubuntu Gutsy Gibbon release candidate by Tech source from bohol </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/8.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/8.04/</guid>
      <description> Giving new life to old computers by Cape Cod Times Pre-Release Review: Xubuntu 8.04 Hardy Heron by Tillamook Rage Xubuntu 8.04 Hardy Heron: Linux Finally Caters to the Public by Tillamook Rage Xubuntu Hardy Heron is Ready for Takeoff by Tech source from bohol </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/8.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/8.10/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu Intrepid Beta Mini-Walkthrough by No Security In Sleep Xubuntu review by Not So Fast </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/9.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/9.04/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu: A Simple Approach To Ubuntu by Linux.com </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/9.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/9.10/</guid>
      <description> Xubuntu 9.10 Review by Dedoimedo.com </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/download/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 24.04 For more information about the release, including release announcement, see the release page.&#xA;Torrents Highly recommended! Torrent (Desktop, 64-bit) Torrent (Minimal, 64-bit) Direct Downloads Click to open! Australia Australia Bulgaria Canada China China France Germany Germany Germany Japan Netherlands Netherlands Russia Sweden Sweden Taiwan United Kingdom United Kingdom United States United States Xubuntu 22.04 For more information about the release, including release announcement, see the release page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Everyone can participate in the Xubuntu community on many levels, from simply giving advice to fellow Xubuntu users to becoming a maintainer of core packages. Any contribution, even the smallest, is valued. We welcome everybody to improve Xubuntu and spread Free Software!&#xA;Artwork If you are of the artistic type, you can take part in making the Xubuntu desktop look better by contributing artwork and helping design the various visual aspects of Xubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help &amp; Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/</guid>
      <description>Documentation Documentation is shipped with every release of Xubuntu and is available through the Help enty in the application menu or by clicking here if you are running Xubuntu.&#xA;Online Documentation&#xA;Release Notes If you are installing or using Xubuntu and have run into a problem, please read the release documents for your release to learn about common bugs and known fixes to them.&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04 Xubuntu 22.04 Browse All Releases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Releases</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releases/</guid>
      <description>A new Xubuntu version is released every 6 months. Regular Xubuntu releases are supported for 9 months and the LTS (Long Term Support) releases for 3 years. LTS releases are released every 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 22.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 20.04 or 21.10 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read JammyUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application; In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo; if you are using 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 22.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 22.04 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read KineticUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo;, and change it if otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 23.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 23.04 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read ManticUpgrades on help.ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo;, and change it if otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Xubuntu 24.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can easily upgrade over the network with the following procedure. Upgrades from Xubuntu 22.04 or 23.10 are supported. For all other Ubuntu systems, please read NobleUpgrades on ubuntu.com.&#xA;Run the update-manager application. In Update Manager, click the Settings&amp;hellip; button, and enter your password to start the Software Sources application. Select the sub menu Updates from the Software Sources application. Confirm the &amp;ldquo;Notify me of a new Ubuntu version:&amp;rdquo; option is set to &amp;ldquo;For any new version&amp;rdquo; if you are using 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/10.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/10.04/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 10.04 LTS, Alsa and gnome-screensaver were replaced with Pulseaudio and xscreensaver respectively. The Ubuntu Software Centre was introduced as the default package manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 10.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/10.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/10.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 10.10 introduced Parole as the default media player. Brasero and the Gnome task manager were replaced by Xfburn and the Xfce4-taskmanager respectively. The Bluebird theme from the Shimmer Project was introduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/11.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/11.04/</guid>
      <description>Based on Xfce 4.8, Xubuntu 11.04 introduced editable menus and a new icon theme based on Elementary. The top panel was joined by a dock-like bottom panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 11.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/11.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/11.10/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 11.10, gThumb was introduced as the new image viewer tool. Mousepad was replaced by Leafpad and LightDM became the new login manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/12.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/12.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 12.04 LTS incorporated many changes, including changes to the default shortcuts. The Pulseaudio volume control (pavucontrol) was introduced as replacement for xfce4-mixer. Along with the 12.04 release, the new Xubuntu logo saw daylight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 12.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/12.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/12.10/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 12.10, Xfce 4.10 was introduced. The menu saw some reorganisation with setting related items moved to the Settings Manager. The documentation was completely rewritten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 13.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/13.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/13.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 13.04 was intended as a maintenance release with few new features. Updates to documentation were included with new versions of Catfish and Parole. GIMP and Gnumeric were reintroduced after a decision to set the target size to 1GB. From Xubuntu 13.04, regular releases would be supported for only 9 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 13.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/13.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/13.10/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 13.10, a new Xfce4 Settings Manager was joined by a new display settings dialogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/14.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/14.04/</guid>
      <description>New features and applications for Xubuntu 14.04 LTS included Xfdesktop 4.11 and Mugshot user account profile tool. MenuLibre replaced Alacarte as the menu editor and and Light locker became the default login manager, also replacing xscreensaver. Whisker menu was added as the default menu applet in the panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 14.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/14.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/14.10/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 14.10, only a few new features were included; a new Power management applet was added to the panel and the window cycling dialog allowed items to be focused with a mouseclick. Users of Xubuntu 14.10 saw the inclusion of pink highlights, highlighting the ease with which changes can be made to the desktop by users if they didn&amp;rsquo;t get on with the default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/15.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/15.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 15.04 introduced Xfce 4.12 with some new features landing in addition to many bugfixes over Xfce 4.10/4.11 components.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 15.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/15.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/15.10/</guid>
      <description>In Xubuntu 15.10, LibreOffcice Calc and Writer replaces Gnumeric and Abiword respectively. A new icon theme is shipped to make LibreOffice look more integrated with the rest of the system. Greybird gets an accesibility version for the window manager theme. Xfce4 Panel Switch is included for backup and restoration of panel with 5 default presets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/16.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/16.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.04 is an LTS version. In 16.04, Ubuntu Software Center was replaced by GNOME Software. Winners from a community wallpaper contest were included with the release for the second time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/16.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/16.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.10 was mostly a maintenance release in which the migration of Xfce to GTK3 was prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 16.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/16.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/16.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 16.10 (Yakkety Yak)&#xA;Known Issues Installer Issues Various virtual machine issues can show up. More so with VirtualBox or VMWare. General Issues 792085 Automatic remount of safely removed usb 3.0 drive Xubuntu Issues 1631715 Password needed twice restarting from suspend Thunar 1311926 Thunar file order changes when renaming 1512120 Thunar crashes on file renaming 1514912 Thunar crash while copying 1540186 Thunar crash while dragging and dropping Changes Thunar Add upstream bugzilla patch to reduce crashes on file move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/17.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/17.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 17.04 was mostly a maintenance release in which the migration of Xfce to GTK3 was prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 17.04 (Zesty Zapus)&#xA;Xubuntu 17.04 will be supported for 9 months until January 2018. If you need Long Term Support, it is recommended you use Xubuntu 16.04 LTS instead.&#xA;Several Xfce panel plugins and applications have been ported to GTK+ 3, paving the way for improved theming and further development. Core Xfce libraries exo and libxfce4ui have also been updated with full GTK+ 3 support, the latter adding support for Glade development in Xubuntu with the installation of &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;libxfce4ui-glade&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/17.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/17.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 17.10 was mostly a maintenance release in which the migration of Xfce to GTK3 was prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 17.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/17.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Notable Changes Incompatibility with BIOS in certain Lenovo, Acer systems A bug in the Linux 4.13 kernel shipped in Ubuntu 17.10 can leave users unable to update any of their BIOS settings, including their system’s boot order, after booting this version of Ubuntu.&#xA;A kernel with a fix for this issue will be available in zesty-updates shortly, but, the Ubuntu 17.10 installer images still contain the kernel with this bug. Users with affected systems should not upgrade to Ubuntu 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/18.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/18.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 18.04 is an LTS release which was released in April 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Notable Issues Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation. We do however aim to test all the possible methods of installation (including for OEM and using encryption) available either on a virtual machine or on hardware (where hardware has been used during testing then Xubuntu QA will where possible make that known on the iso testing tracker).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/18.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/18.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 18.10 was the last release to support 32-bit architectures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 18.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/18.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading from 18.04 For 32 bit installations this is disabled and currently out of our control.&#xA;Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation. We do however aim to test all the possible methods of installation (including for OEM and using encryption) available either on a virtual machine or on hardware (where hardware has been used during testing then Xubuntu QA will where possible make that known on the iso testing tracker).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/19.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/19.04/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Dropping 32-bit Images In December, the team voted to discontinue 32-bit images for Xubuntu 19.04 and forward. If you want to continue using Xubuntu with 32-bit architectures, Xubuntu 18.04 is supported for 3 years, and the Xubuntu package set can be installed from the Minimal CD.&#xA;Installer Issues It must be noted that it is close to impossible for our small team of testers to be in a position to work through all the varying parameters available during installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/19.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/19.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 19.10 features Xfce 4.14, released in August 2019 after nearly 4.5 years of development. Backed by GTK 3 and other modern technologies, Xfce 4.14 includes many new features, improved HiDPI support, and the same great performance for which Xfce is known.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 19.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/19.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Known Issues Installer Issues System doesn&amp;rsquo;t boot after installation - Legacy mode / 2 disks (1847898) General Issues GNOME Font Viewer: Crashes in the live environment (1845362) Ubiquity: Chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Xfce Pulseaudio Plugin: Multiple notifications displayed if multiple Pulseaudio plugins added to panel (1769775) Xfce Task Manager: Tooltips become unresponsive (1740578, fix committed upstream) Ubuntu Generic Release Note The main Ubuntu release note covers both many of the other packages we carry and more generic issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/20.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/20.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 20.04 is an LTS release which was released in April 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 20.04 &amp;ldquo;Focal Fossa&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 20.04 was released on Thursday, April 23, 2020 and will be supported for three years until Saturday, April 29, 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 20.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Screenshots Major Updates Removals Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues System doesn&amp;rsquo;t boot after installation - Legacy mode / 2 disks (1847898) grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Graphical Issues AMD Graphics: Block staircase display with side-by-side monitors of different pixel widths (1873895, Fixed upstream, SRU expected for 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/20.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/20.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 20.10 is a regular release which was released in October 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/20.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 20.10 &amp;ldquo;Groovy Gorilla&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 20.10 was released on Thursday, October 22, 2020 and will be supported for nine months until Thursday, July 22, 2021. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 20.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Removals Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) Graphical Issues AMD Graphics: Block staircase display with side-by-side monitors of different pixel widths (1873895, Fixed upstream, SRU expected for 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/21.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/21.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 21.04 is a regular release which was released in April 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/21.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/21.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 21.10 is a regular release which was released in October 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/22.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/22.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 22.04 is an LTS release which was released in April 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 22.04 &amp;ldquo;Jammy Jellyfish&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 22.04 will be released on Thursday, April 21, 2022, and will be supported for three years until April 2025. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 22.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1942987, 1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/22.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/22.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 22.10 is a regular release which was released in October 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 22.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/22.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 22.10 &amp;ldquo;Kinetic Kudu&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 22.10 will be released on Thursday, October 20, 2022, and will be supported for nine months until July 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 22.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues grub-installer chooses which drive to install to with no user input (964331) OEM installation uses the wrong slideshow (1842047) No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/23.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/23.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 23.04 is a regular release which was released in April 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 23.04 &amp;ldquo;Lunar Lobster&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 23.04 was be released on Thursday, April 20, 2023, and will be supported for nine months until January 2023. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 23.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/23.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/23.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 23.10 is a regular release which was released in October 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 23.10 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/23.10/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 23.10 &amp;ldquo;Mantic Minotaur&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 23.10 was released on Thursday, October 12, 2023, and will be supported for nine months until July 2024. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 23.10, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Appearance Updates Hardware Support Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 24.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/24.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/24.04/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 24.04 is an LTS release which was released in April 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 24.04 Release Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/releasedocs/24.04/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Xubuntu 24.04 &amp;ldquo;Noble Numbat&amp;rdquo; release notes!&#xA;Xubuntu 24.04 was released on Thursday, April 25, 2024, and will be supported for three years until April 2027. For general information and the latest updates for Xubuntu 24.04, check out the release page on xubuntu.org.&#xA;Known Issues Ubuntu Common Release Notes Major Updates Updates Changelogs Known Issues Installer Issues GRUB menu not displayed for dual-boot system installation (2060624) Installer may select two root (/) partitions (2060896) No shutdown prompt after installation (1944519) However, you should be able to press the Enter key to continue with the reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 6.06</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/6.06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/6.06/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 6.06 is the first Xubuntu release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 6.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/6.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/6.10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 7.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/7.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/7.04/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 7.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/7.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/7.10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 8.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/8.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/8.04/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 8.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/8.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/8.10/</guid>
      <description>Xubuntu 8.10 was the sixth Xubuntu release. Listen was the default media player and Catfish and Seahorse were introduced. Support for encrypted private directories was added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.04</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/9.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/9.04/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 9.10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/release/9.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/release/9.10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
